Confession of a High School “Mean Girl” by Clarimonde

I never meant to kill Melissa Dodd, but that girl brought it on herself.

Most people don’t understand the concept “survival of the fittest”. They think natural selection means the fastest, or the strongest, or the smartest will always survive. It’s not true. The ones that always survive are those that best adapt to the world around them. There’s a certain type of high school girl that understands this concept better than anyone else. The girls that are not afraid to claw their way to the top of the food chain. They call us “mean girls” now. Please. We may be mean, but nature is the cruelest bitch of all.

I started my ascent in middle school and by sophomore year, I was unofficially crowned queen bee. Janet Spencer was more popular and infinitely prettier, but someone had spread an unfortunate rumor that she modeled incontinence pads and gave out hand jobs to homeless people. I was thin and attractive with a squad of equally thin and attractive girls vying for my approval. The fact that I did daily three-mile jogs at 6:00 a.m. and endlessly sipped on diet cola to stop the growling in the pit of my stomach was a small price to pay.

By contrast, Melissa was what we referred to as an “unfortunate”. A growth spurt in eighth grade left her towering above her peers at almost six feet. This meant she lumbered from class to class with a stoop, trying to make herself as small as possible. A combination of bad skin and flowery teeth sealed her status as an awkward spaz. I don’t remember who christened her “the Jabberwocky” but it certainly stuck. Melissa was so far down the social ladder that she was underneath it.

Then she did something unthinkable, she decided to climb.

I was having lunch in the quad with Becky and Gina when it happened. It was on a rare sunny day in February, the type of day where everyone lingers a little longer before going to class. Gina shoveled down her salad while Becky prattled on about how Mike was spending too much time at practice. I don’t see those girls much now. Becky has three kids and is head of the PTA while Gina’s a Sunday school teacher. I suppose that’s how they deal with it. Becky tries to be the perfect mom and Gina talks about God.

The three of us were facing the entrance of the cafeteria when we saw the new and improved Melissa Dodd.

“No way!”

The words rumbled from the back of my throat.

Somehow, our favorite, buck-toothed ugly duckling had turned herself into a plausible swan. Wherever she had bought her clothes, however much she had spent covering up that oozing acne, it had all been worth it.

We looked on in silence as Aaron Peterson came walking towards her. He wasn’t exactly MVP, but he was a sweet, lean basketball player who plenty of girls lusted after. He smiled at her and they started chatting. Like she was an actual person. As she walked away, he turned back, obviously checking out her non-ass in last season’s drainpipes.

“What the fuck was that?” whispered Gina.

“Aaron Peterson just checked out the Jabberwocky” hissed Becky.

Something had to be done. In some ways, it was inevitable what happened. That girl never stood a chance.

Becky didn’t take long to convince, and Gina was a complete pushover. Although it was still warm outside, the air in the equipment shed was damp. I shivered a little, examining the plastic mask in my hand. We bought them on discount from an old store downtown. I called dibs on the tiger mask, Becky went with the elephant and Gina had the zebra. It wasn’t that complicated. We had watched Melissa for a week. She did long jump on Tuesdays after school. She was pretty good, I’ll give her that. It was a small compensation for looking like the love child of Paul Bunion and Allison Janney.

We listened to the sounds of the track team, trying not to fall asleep. It got late, and the voices began to trail off. Melissa always stuck around and was one of the last to hit the showers. Don’t ask me why. The girl was a weirdo. By the time Gina cracked open the door and called Melissa’s name, it was already getting dark and she was the last one on the field. Our old gym teacher, Miss Hettinger, was already inside, probably desperate to get home to the girlfriend none of us supposedly knew about. Melissa’s outline appeared by the door and Becky yanked her inside. I turned on the light. Melissa wasn’t stupid. She knew that she was alone, that no one was coming to check on her and that the three people wearing masks in the shed were going to use that bat and hockey sticks. She held up a hand.

“Please, don’t!”

And then we beat her. Not much, but enough so she wouldn’t put up a fight. When we finished, I told Becky and Gina to grab her arms and legs. Becky started to chicken out.

“What if she tells someone. What if we’re caught?”

I squeezed her hand.

“And what if she goes on like this? The girl needs to know her place.”

“Yeah, yeah you’re right.”

I placed the cloth over Melissa’s face and began to pour the gallon of water I’d swiped from the cafeteria. She tossed her head from side to side and twisted to get free, but the girls held her tight. I continued to pour as she coughed and sputtered, the water filling her lungs. Her squirming weakened as the bottle got lighter and lighter and by the time it was empty, Melissa Dodd had stopped moving.

I’ll admit it, I got carried away. It’s not like I had a lot of practice with stuff like that. I’d just read about it when I did a class project on apartheid. You need to understand. The girl was out of control and we had to put things right. It was Gina that suggested we dump her in the lake. I noticed Melissa’s expression as we laid her on the piece of old tarp. It was one of mild surprise, her gray eyes fixed on nothing in this world. One of her running shoes came off as we carried the rolled-up tarp to Becky’s car. When I picked it up, I saw she’d written “I am a champion” on the heel. So hopeful. So pathetic.

It was completely dark by the time we pulled up to the shore. The moon was a thin slit in the sky and no stars were out that night. Since we had nothing to weigh the body down, we waded out in our clothes and let the current take it. And then she was gone. Nothing more than ripples and whispers.

People say a body is never really gone. It eventually pops up again to point the finger at you. That’s also not true. We could’ve been found out a hundred times, but we never were. It’s not like we weren’t on edge. We were high school girls that had been through a traumatic experience. Nobody ever questioned us, and the police never found Melissa Dodd. I thought that was the end of it. That is, until two months later.

I had woken up to heavy wheezing and the soft sound of paper being crumpled. Opening my eyes, I saw a familiar face sitting at my desk, scribbling furiously on a page in my journal. Numerous other pages lay balled up and scattered on the floor.

Melissa mouthed the words aloud as pen scratched against paper.

“One, two! One, two! And through and through,

The vorpal blade went snicker-snack!

She left her dead, and with her head,

She went galumphing back.”

‘And hast thou slain the Jabberwock?

Come to my arms, my beamish boy!

O frabjous day! Callooh! Callay!’

She chortled in her joy.”

She stopped, finally noticing I was awake.

“Well hello.”

I sat up.

“Melissa, what the fuck are you doing in my room?”

“Look, I’m sorry, but when I knocked, and you didn’t answer, I just thought I’d come in and wait. And there you were. I couldn’t wait outside for too long.”

My mood lifted, and a wave of relief washed over me. The little upstart had survived after all. She had woken up and swam to shore, good as new. Maybe the frigid temperature of the water did some damage and she had some sort of amnesia? I decided to play it cool.

“Is this about what happened to you? About when you went missing?”

“Missing? No, I don’t know anything about that. I’m here to talk to you about something. Something pretty personal.”

I shifted my body towards desk to take a closer look. Her lank tendrils of dark hair were damp and pushed back behind her ears, like she’d just stepped out of the shower. Her polo shirt was rumpled, and the collar was stained with mud.

“Okay then Melissa. What’s the problem?”

“Oh well, where do I begin? This is a little messy. A tricky situation. I suppose I’d better just to get this whole thing out in the open.”

Her lips parted in a faint smile. I noticed that her front teeth were mottled.

“My problem is all this business with Aaron.”

“Aaron Peterson? What does he have to do with anything?”

Her eyebrows gathered inward, and she angled her head. The expression made her features look threatening.

“You know I was supposed to meet him after practice. He must think I’m such a flake.”

There was a soft tapping on the door.

She wheezed a little and started coughing. I noticed that one of her trainers was missing. That same secret smile spread across her face again.

“I need you to do me a favor. Take him to our special spot. He’ll listen to you. Tell him I’m waiting for that date”.

The rapping at the door turned to full-on banging that drew a swift, alarmed glance from Melissa.

“Do it!” she rasped sharply, her pale eyes burning into mine with an urgent malice.

The pounding grew louder and louder until I felt it resonating in my head. The sound echoed in my ears for hours after I woke up screaming.

I didn’t take Aaron to the lake after Melissa’s first visit, or the second, or even the twenty-second. We all have that point though, where everything gives way and the unthinkable becomes plausible.

It was easier than I thought in the end. A teenage boy will go anywhere after a few drinks and the vague promise of getting lucky. I made sure to drop a couple valium in his brewski before going out on the boat. My mother had a sizeable collection of meds back then. It didn’t take him long to pass out and he barely stirred when I tied the tire chains around his ankles. He looked so peaceful and angelic as he sank beneath the surface, like Leo at the end of Titanic.

You would think that’d be enough, but Melissa wasn’t done. What can I say? I think girlfriend got a taste for it. I give her one guy a year and she leaves me alone. That’s the agreement. She still likes them young too, baby-faced varsity all-stars. I once gave her a middle-aged sad sack that I hooked up with in a bar off the interstate. I thought he was easy pickings. The bitch didn’t leave me sleep for six weeks until I made it up to her.

It’s getting harder for me now. I haven’t aged like Becky or Gina. I don’t sleep well, and the booze can’t be doing me any good. I’m still here though. That counts for something. I’m adapting and I’m surviving.

I better go. I need to get ready for a date.

FOXTROT-ALPHA-ZULU-6-7-6 - ALL PERSONNEL LEAVE THE AREA by GeoronimoTheThird

Should you hear this warning at ANY POINT, leave the area immediately. Do not stop and help others leave, there is no time. If you are lucky, you may escape the radius in the provided 1 minute and 30 seconds.

This code may come over a loudspeaker in a shopping mall, your headphones while you listen to music, or through the television while you watch. Whatever the case, the only advice is to leave all pets and personal belongings and attempt to reach a safe distance.

It is the code used to inform all personnel of the government agency known as ‘Apholith’ to evacuate before testing begins. The radius itself varies, it could cover your present building, or stretch across your city.

Should you fail to make it out of the radius in time you will invariably find all escapes blocked, whether by locked doors or roadblocks. The roadblock security will be armed, escaping will no longer be an option.

The warning is issued across all available devices, and may seem like a mistake or perhaps a mishearing, but have no doubt it is not, and you are in terrible, imminent danger.

Apholith will be deploying one of three tests in your area, operation Hooper, operation Highland, or operation Leveau. Each of these operations are named for the test subjects that the project centers upon, Simon Hooper, Lila Highland or Brandon Leveau, and will be referred to from this point onwards as ‘the subjects’. All were unwitting volunteers for Apholith experiments, revolving around the research and weaponization of astral projection. Each test was based off of the strides and breakthroughs of operation ‘Vincent’, also known as ‘E37’, carried out in a secure bunker in Avery Hills. These tests are designed to measure the effectiveness of these weapons.

Should you fail to make it to a safe distance before in the allotted 1 minute and 30 seconds, your only option becomes to survive the test duration, a task that I assure you is nigh impossible. The precise activation point of the subject will be somewhere close to the centre of the test area. The test duration will also vary, and you can only hope your fellow participants prove too numerous and the time runs out before you are targeted by Hooper, Highland or Leveau.

The best option is to move as far as you can towards the edges of the test area without leaving, as you will be shot upon escaping. However it is strongly suggested you remain on the ground floor. If you are fortunate there may be a nook or corner that sits just beyond the subjects area of influence, allowing you to hide where it cannot harm you. If it becomes clear that the subjects are capable of reaching you, your next best option now is to find as much metal barring, wiring and caging as possible with which to surround yourself. This may make obscure you at least somewhat from the subjects, should it fail to do so, they will surely execute you without prejudice.

Be warned, the subjects themselves are not easy to spot, they appear in their once human forms, but they have the capability to shift the form of their limbs to sharpened blades, bludgeoning instruments and any kind of basic implement without moving parts.

When the test is over, you will hear the code Hotel-Whiskey-Polo-4-0-7. At this point the subjects will dissipate as they are remotely deactivated, however YOU ARE NOT SAFE. The test premises will be immediately scrubbed of any surviving participants.

In the time before armed forces arrive to strike you off and tally you as a test survivor, the only way they will not find you is to remove or destroy the chip, introduced during government vaccinations. This chip shows your location and heart rate. You have three options:

Locate an extremely high powered electromagnet and press it to your upper arm.

Find an enclosed, lead lined room to block the signal.

Use an implement to slice open your upper arm, the chip is located around an inch under the skin.

Now hide as best you can and keep silent until they have passed. The only remaining option now is to wait until your premises have been completely cleaned and all bodies are removed. Until this point, it is not safe to leave as there will be armed agents in the area.

I wish I could say you will never hear this warning, but the tests will continue. I was unable to shut Apholith down, now all I can do is hope this reaches as many ears as possible. You may not believe any of this, but I implore you to commit it to memory, it may one day save your life.

Have you ever experienced something that's more than deja vu? by zobaleenie

Apologies for the formatting, as i am on my phone. I was also unsure where to post this, so bare with me. I'm not really sure what it is that I experience. Deja vu is the feeling that you've done something before. My experiences are like this, but halfway through this feeling I remember that I have dreamt the exact scenario that is playing out. It takes a while to realise this because these dreams are of normal boring everyday tasks, so not really dreams that stand out. I don't have these experiences through anything in particular, no world events that I could be stopped or anything.

One example of this sticks out in my mind very clearly. I started college 6 years ago, and on my first day I was sat in one of my classes, and I had the feeling of deja vu. As the room filled up with students, it hit me as clear as day that I had dreamt about this exact scenario. The tables were in a horse shape around the board, and I was sat to the right at the back. I knew what the lesson was going to be about before we had even started it. As soon as everyone started introducing themselves I knew who they were and their anecdotes that they all had to relay to the other students. I knew that the teacher would have trouble with the computer because it was new and he didn't know how to use it. I even knew what colour the walls of the classroom were! Stupid things that wouldn’t really stand out to you. I sat there and thought of everything that would happen a couple of seconds before each event unfolded.

I remember a lot of instances like this, but none of them very significant. I told my partner the other night that I had dreamt about us sitting in bed watching a particular film and ignoring the dog trying to get up on the bed. He just laughed at me. Why would he believe me? I’m a big fan of horror so he probably thought I was spinning an elaborate paranormal tale. He’s very cynical like That! I’ve lsent to just keep my mouth shut and ride the experience through, often chuckling at how strange it all feels to have experienced it all before. And it’s also strange that even though I have these dreams months beforehand can remember dreaming it like it was the night before.

I'm not really sure if this is all leading up to something. I can't predict the lottery or anything, I have these dreams months and months before the events actually unfold. And I would keep a dream journal, but these dreams are a rarity; not every dream turns out to happen in my conscious state. I'll just have to wait and see if this becomes major. People have thrown the term “psychic out there” – in not being funny or anything, but why would I be dreaming about every day things if it was part of something bigger? I don’t want to seem crazy.

How an Office Crush Saved My Marriage by DexKnightley

Last year was probably the hardest year my wife and I have ever endured. We have been trying to conceive a child for months, and after getting frustrated, we went to the doctor to get tested and found out I was sterile. In June, her parents were both killed in a freak boating accident. Some other boater was drinking and driving their boat, caused an accident, and it was apparently very messy. My wife, being an only child, and was very close with her parents was devastated. She made comments about how she has no family, and because of me (and my sterility) she was never going to have one. I chalked that comment up to the hurt she was feeling and lashing out at me. Knowing later we’d likely talk about adoption, or other options we may have.

Understandably so, my wife just kind of shut down following the death of her parents. People kept telling me that the best thing I can do, is just be there for her. I have done my best to do so. I’ve been keeping the house clean, making all of the meals. Just keeping it together for the both of us. She hardly speaks to me. Mostly just sleeps, watches TV, and when she does say something, it’s usually very negative. Through a lot of gentle nudging and pushing, she started going to therapy, and going to a support group. She started going back to work in September, but even then, she just goes in, does her cubicle work, and then comes home to the TV or goes straight to bed.

It’s been hard, but I love her. I constantly remind myself of my wedding, and the vow I made, “In sickness and in health.” This is just something that I am patiently waiting for. When tragedy like this strikes, people do separate themselves from you a bit. I don’t blame my friends for giving us extra space. My wife isn’t exactly a joy to be around, and if you don’t know what to say, it can be extremely challenging. As a result, I don’t see my friends too much right now, and my family just upsets her because it reminds her that she has none left.

I know this may come across as an excuse, or justification for what I am about to share. But, life has been lonely for me. Most people where I work have some idea of what is going on. They don’t ask me the normal questions I hear them asking others. They don’t ask me what my weekend plans are. They don’t ask me for drinks after work. Likely, they are tired of me saying I cannot join because I have to go take care of my wife. Have you ever played that game called Telephone? Where one person taps the other on the shoulder, or whispers a phrase into their ear, and this continues through people, and then you see how the message has changed or distorted the more people that play. I think that’s what has happened in my office. I hear some people say my wife is on her deathbed, some question her existence, other’s say that her parents were murdered. I’ve heard a lot. I really just wanted someone to talk to.

Enter Aella. She’s been working in my office since October, and I noticed her right away. Tall, blonde, wonderful features, incredibly nice, and a smile that lights up a room. I saw her a lot at first, because her lunch break was the same as mine. I’d awkwardly stand in silence a few feet from her when we microwave our lunches, only nodding acknowledgement when we would see each other at first. I never worked with her, she works in a different department, Human Resources, I think. When the microwaves dinged, we’d grab our food then go to the break room. She’d sit with some coworkers she befriended, and I’d go sit in the corner table, by myself. I’d often pretend to read a book, but since I’ve been longing for conversation for so long, I would just listen to everyone else’s conversations. I know Aella is a single mother, her child was 6 months old in November, and just moved back in with her parents after a messy break up.

Things went on this way all through November. Thanksgiving came and went. I bought a pre-made chicken dinner that I ate with my wife. She mumbled something as we ate, but I couldn’t quite hear, when I asked to repeat, she just shook her head.

Everything changed on December 4th. It is a day that will forever be burned into my memory. I sat down for lunch in my corner table, and Aella walked up to me, with her lunch and spoke to me.

“No microwave today?” She said as she lifted up her lunch in a sort of gesture.

“Just a sandwich. Nothing special.”

“My normal lunch buddies are out sick today, care for some company?” It seemed like a question, but she was already pulling up a chair and sitting down.

My heart felt like it was beating out of my chest. Nobody ever talks to me, and never in my life have I ever ate lunch with someone so attractive (aside from my wife). “Of course!” I responded, hopefully not sounding too eager.

Our 30 minute lunch went by in what felt like the blink of an eye. We ended up becoming friends on social media, and started sending messages through its messaging app. Over the next couple weeks I talked with her a lot. She knows I am married, we made it clear that we both are just friends, and I learned a lot about her child. I likely overshared about my year, and how hard it has been, and when I did, she put her hand on mine. Saying how sorry she was, and that she’s my friend, and she’s here if I need anything. I don’t remember what day it was, but I don’t want to keep any secrets from my wife, so I went home and spoke to her one day.

“Honey, I made a new friend at work today!” I always add a little excitement and happiness when I talk to her, hopefully allow her to feed off of some of my positivity.

“So?” She said ver flatly.

“Yes, her name is Aella. I think you and her would be good friends. She’s nice, same age as us, and said she’s interested in meeting you sometime too.” I did purposefully leave out the fact she has a child.

“Why the Hell would I want to make friends with her? If you like her so much, why don’t you just go sleep with her?” She said, staring daggers at me.

“Honey, you know I’d never do that. You are the only one for me.” I said, trying to hold her hand in mine. She pulled away and put her hands behind her back.

“Whatever.” She just said and then she looks aways and doesn’t look back, and any attempt to get in the way or speak to her are all futile.

Life went on like this for a couple more weeks. I looked forward to my lunches with Aella. They were the highlight of my day, and I think she was enjoying them too. She smiled every time we walked by one another, and one Friday, she asked if I wanted to get drinks with her and a couple other co-workers after work. I texted my wife, telling her my plans and asking her if it was okay, she responded with “Why do I care?” I left it at that, and went out.

It felt like so long since I’ve been to a bar, and had a beer, and sat in a circle and talked with anyone. After my first beer, I felt myself loosen up, and get better at talking. There was country music on the speakers, and I could see people around the bar. Definitely a dive bar with a lot of regulars. At some point, Aella excused herself to go to the restroom, leaving me and her two friends, Carmen, and Francine. Which of course prompts the girls to say things that they normally wouldn’t say around Aella.

“So what’s the deal with you two? Do you like her?” Carmen jumps straight to the point.

“I think she’s great. Pretty much the only friend I talk to right now.” I reply.

“Friend?” Giggles Francine.

“Yeah, you guys know I am married.” I say while holding up my hand with my wedding ring on.

“I mean, we know.” Carmen stares at me “We also know that you could do better, with someone that actually likes you.” She gets an almost evil grin on her face.

I squint my eyes a little bit at that, “It’s just a rough patch, there’s been a lot of bad things this year.”

“Jesus, you are either way too nice, too stupid, too naive or all of the above!” Francine practically yells.

I just shrug my shoulders at this, and Aella now returns to the table and sits down. Carmen grabs Francine. “I love this song, let’s dance!” Leaving Aella and myself alone at the table. I look down at the table of empty beer bottles, counting 14 empty bottles.

“Jesus, did we drink that many already?”

“Apparently!” She laughs. It’s an amazing laugh. It feels like liquid gold on my heart. Reminds me of when I used to hear my wife’s laugh.

I must have made a face because Aella looks at me and grabs my hand, “None of that, we are dancing!”

She took me to the dance floor, and we danced. I felt like I was in Jr High and felt awkward the whole time. As the night went on, I drank more beer, got better at dancing, and had the best time I’ve had in what feels like forever.

Eventually the night comes to an end because the bar is closing. As we say our goodbyes, Carmen is driving, pulls Francis into the passenger side of the car, leaving Aella and I outside. I heard something about alone time.

“That was fun. Thanks for inviting me out. You have no idea how much it means. I haven’t been out of the house-” I was abruptly cut off by Aella leaning in and kissing me on the mouth. It wasn’t anything spectacular. I was caught off guard, I didn’t open my mouth any more than it was already open mid-sentence. It lasted for maybe a few seconds. Felt like much longer.

“I had a good time too.” She says, after she pulls back, and pushes some of the hair from her face back behind her ear. “See you Monday!”

I stood there for a while. Contemplating what had just happened. Did I just cheat on my wife? I would never do that! Can I still be friends with Aella now? Was it just the alcohol? I headed home. I drove. Probably shouldn’t have because I had some beers, but I wasn’t thinking clearly. I did make it home safely. My wife was already sleeping, or pretending to sleep. She does that too. I knew she wasn’t going to ask me about my night. Even though I laid awake most of the night replaying those few seconds in my head over and over again. Only falling asleep when I started seeing the sun come up.

Eventually I woke. When I woke up, my wife was still there. She was looking at me with a look on her face that I haven’t seen in a while. It was a face that was looking at me, instead of through me.

“I know I haven’t been good to you in a while.” She started with.

“It’s okay, I know-” She cut me off with a finger to signal that she had more to say and has been practicing what to say.

“I feel like I lost everything, and have nothing to gain, and I blamed you for it. I think a part of me still does. Which I know is not fair. I promise to work on it, though.” I didn’t say anything, and just hugged her. This felt like an enormous breakthrough, and I didn’t want to ruin it. I didn’t talk to Aella at all that weekend. When Monday came around, when I saw Aella in the morning, she was dressed up nicely today. Looking very good. When we crossed paths, there was this nervousness from her. Figuring she is just embarrassed about the kiss. Later, I get an office email from her saying that we needed to talk alone, and that we should have lunch outside of the office today, at a small restaurant across the street. I agreed.

When we sat down for lunch, she got right to it.

“Look, I know you are married but what I did on Friday, I meant it. I have feelings for you, and I’ve never felt anything like this before. You can’t tell me you don’t feel it too?”

Her speech took me by surprise. I had to think about what I wanted to say. “Look, Aella, I have no plans to cheat or to leave my wife. I made her a promise, and her and I had a small breakthrough this weekend. She is getting better, and I know I will too. I’d love to stay your friend though.”

“I am not sure if I can handle that,” She said between tears, “You are all I think about. I know you and I are meant to be. Not you and her. I’d never treat you like this.”

“I know it’s easy to say that. You’ll never know until you have lived through something like that though.” I reasoned.

“I am sorry I brought it up.” With that, she got up and ran out of the restaurant.

She called out sick for the rest of the day at work. Then she called out the next day, and the next, until she was out all week. I sent her a few messages, asking her if she was okay, but I didn’t want to push it. I didn’t realize that me, in my broken state, was even desirable at all. I never saw her again. She was terminated from her job because she just disappeared. Hadn’t talked to anyone at work, didn’t answer any of her phone calls. Nothing.

Until Saturday. There was a knock on the door. There was a lady I never met before, holding a baby. I was cleaning, doing my Saturday chores, and my wife was in the next room watching television.

“Are you Jason?” She said holding up a sheet of paper.

“Yes, that is me. Who are you?”

“My name is Samantha, with the support of Child State Department and Protective Services.” She holds up some sort of identification badge. “I am here with 9 month old Octavia. It is my understanding you are unaware that you are the father.”

At this point, my wife appears from the other room, and the woman at the door notices her. “Oh, umm. We can do this somewhere else.”

“Maybe we should, but first, how is this possible? For one, I am sterile, and I have only been with my wife for the last five years.”

“I understand, sir. You have to understand, though, I hear this a lot from married me.”

“I suppose so.” I replied, “Who is the mother?”

She holds up the piece of paper “You ever know anyone by the name of Aella? She has you listed as the father on the birth certificate.”

“Yes I know her, but, what is going on?”

“I am sorry to be the one to inform you, but she took her own life a couple days ago. She left a note, addressed to you, and with a way for you to find us.” She paused. “Now, about the matter of the baby.”

At this point my wife walked up and took the baby, and spoke up. “It’s fine, we will work through it, and we’ll work on his transgressions for the sake of the baby.”

This seemed to satisfy the government agent, and she had some paperwork for us to sign, a couple numbers for us to call and follow-up with and she was on her way.

My wife now, sitting on the couch, holding and playing with the baby. Me, still in shock. I opened the note she left:

“Dear Jason,

I am afraid I cannot go on knowing that we cannot be together.

I have known you for longer than you may be aware of. I’ve watched you for quite some time. Taking me months before working up the courage to work where you work, and forever for me to talk to you in the office. I’ll always love you. Even though I cannot have you, maybe I can do something great for you, as you once did for me, many years ago.

This is Octavia. Your daughter. Her birthday is June 16th.

With All the Love I Have Left, Aella”

I couldn’t really think of what to say. I was still in shock, all I could say to my wife.

“This makes no sense. I haven’t even known her for a year.”

“It doesn’t matter. We have what we wanted.” My wife said, then she smiled, for the first time in almost a year.

I changed my walking route with my dog by lordwelshi

I’ve tried posting this elsewhere, but it keeps getting taken down. So this is my last attempt at trying to seek help, or an explanation, or anything. I don’t really know what I’m expecting. Guess I’m just desperate at this point. The pain in my chest and coughing fits still come and go, every few hours, but each time it gets worse and lasts longer.

This all started about a week ago. My wife, Laura, and I had just got home from work. We work at the same place, so we’re always home at the same time, it’s one of the great conveniences in my life. We got home around 5pm, just as it’s starting to turn dark outside. We got in the house, and there was our dog, Trinket, waiting to greet us as usual. Trinket is a border collie/corgi mix, and is adorable. She’s basically a short, compacted border collie with the huge radar-dish ears of a corgi. She’s always very excited to see us after work, probably because we spoil her rotten. Laura and I don’t have children. We can’t have kids, so we got a dog to keep us company, and we absolutely love our Trinket.

We followed our usual routine. I went upstairs to change out of my work clothes and into my waterproof trousers and coat, while Laura put Trinket’s harness on. I came downstairs, grabbed my keys, put my walking boots on, hooked the lead onto Trinket’s harness, and let her pull me out of the front door. Laura, as always, locked the door behind me.

Trinket is always very excited when we go walking, to the point she usually pulls on the lead for the first few minutes until she’s calmed down a bit. Usually I take her along the side streets towards an old disused railway line that has been paved and turned into a cycle-way and footpath. It runs in a straight line for a mile through some woods and alongside a stream, but we’ve done it that many times I got a bit bored with it. I think Trinket was starting to find it a bit dull, too.

So that evening, I decided to try a new route. There’s a stretch of canal footpath that runs for nearly two miles from near the end of our street to an old, disused warehouse which has recently been resurfaced. I tried walking it about a year ago with Trinket, but it was so muddy I just kept sliding around and nearly fell into the canal, so we never took that route again. Well, until that night, anyway.

Everything started out fine. Trinket led the way to the end of our street, and turned to the left, as we usually do. I tugged on her lead, and started to turn right instead. Trinket hesitated, looking at me and turning her head in that inquisitive way dogs seem to do when they wonder just what the hell you’re doing. After a moment, she relented and followed me. The light was fading, and the street lights flickered and buzzed as we walked beneath them. One of them was out completely, but we kept walking until we came to the road bridge that crossed the canal. We crossed it carefully, as the bridge narrows so much there’s no designated pedestrian footpath, but there were no cars on this narrow road, luckily enough.

Trinket and I stepped down onto the canal path. I could hear the gentle lap of water from some unseen run-off drain that poured into the canal. Trinket was excited again; apparently happy we were going to walk on a different route to her familiar walk. I wish we had stuck to our usual path, then maybe I wouldn’t be in the situation I’m in now. What used to be a mud path had been paved over, and the asphalt surface was definitely an improvement over the old dirt footpath.

I remember the deep purple the horizon turned as the sun was setting. Deep shadows loomed over us, the trees that lined the canal path reaching up into the sky. A breeze picked up, cutting through my coat and chilling me to the bone. As we walked, Trinket occasionally stopped and sniffed at the brambles at the edge of the path, before trotting on. Each time we paused at one of these sniffing spots, I would look up and down the path to make sure we weren’t in the way of any other walkers or joggers. Each time I checked, the route ahead and behind were completely empty. We were the only ones on this path.

We only had about a quarter mile to go to the boarded-up warehouse, and I could see its dark, box shape looming ahead. From what I can tell, it used to belong to a shipping company that ran a fleet of canal boats that would travel across the country using the waterways to deliver coal from nearby mines. But I do know the company shut down in the 50s after some kind of incident. It was common knowledge in the area: a couple of workers died in the warehouse after some kind of chemical spill. All that had been found of them was scarred, pitted bones. The warehouse had been kept locked and boarded up ever since.

As we got closer to the warehouse, I began to feel uneasy. I couldn’t quite place my finger on it at the time, but something felt off. It wasn’t quite 6 o’clock, and though it was dark out, there should have been more people on the path. Walkers, joggers, people out fishing, the usual suspects that would be enjoying a brisk winter evening on a peaceful section of canal were nowhere to be seen, and I found that very unsettling. Trinket was on edge too: she was staring off into the low brush, and her hackles were up. She was making these very quiet barks, almost like she was warning something away but didn’t want to be heard. I’d never seen her so nervous.

We got to the warehouse, where I planned to turn around and head back the way we’d come. It was a large building, three storeys tall, that stretched back a good distance from the canal. Huge, sheet metal fencing extended around the entire building, meeting the edges of the wall that fronted the canal path. The doors and windows were all boarded up with the same metal panels. Whoever had closed this warehouse didn’t want anyone getting in. Or anything getting out.

As we turned around, I looked up at one of the sealed windows. It looked different to the other boarded-up windows. I squinted at it, trying to make it out in the dark. There, at the bottom right corner, the metal panel had been bent inwards, a dark hole leading into the interior of the warehouse. It looked like something had struck the metal sheet with some force. I felt like my eyes were being drawn to that hole, like something was pulling at me, trying to get me to climb up and stick my face inside to see what was there, some weird compulsion of curiosity tinged with fear.

“Okay, let’s go home, Trinket,” I said quietly. Trinket looked up at me.

Don’t let people tell you dogs don’t feel emotion like we do. That’s utter bullshit. Trinket was terrified.

We made it about 100 yards when Trinket suddenly stopped. I tugged on her lead, but she would not budge. She was hunkered down to the ground, ears laid flat back against her head, teeth bared in a snarl I had never seen on her before. A low growl rumbled in her throat.

A rustle from the bush she was glaring at made me snap my head around. I stared at the shaking mass of vegetation, holding my breath, heart racing. I jumped as Trinket let out a loud bark. The rustling shifted and vanished, somewhere off to the right, back towards the warehouse.

I yanked on Trinket’s lead, and she followed me as I began to jog along the path, back towards the safety of home. But after a few seconds, the lead snapped taught as Trinket stopped again. I turned to look at her as she stuck her face into some thick grass at the side of the path.

“Come on, let’s go,” I said urgently.

Trinket’s head reappeared from the undergrowth.

There was a bone clenched between her teeth.

Absolute terror gripped me. I didn’t want to look. I didn’t want to know. I wanted to get home, where it’s bright and safe and warm. I didn’t want to know.

I had to know.

Slowly, I moved closer to the clump of grass and bramble. I gingerly moved thorny branches aside, dread sitting in my stomach.

Two human skulls. A ribcage. Femurs.

There were enough remains here for at least 2 people. If it had just been the bones, I think I could have handled it, but it was the gory red strings of torn flesh and ligaments and muscle that still clung to them in places, streaks of crimson blood and the stench of soured meat that tipped me over the edge.

Bile rose in my throat, and I vomited.

“We have to go.” I pulled Trinket away, the bone she had found discarded on the path.

Suddenly there was a loud rustle and a hiss. Trinket growled and barked, pulling so hard on her lead that I nearly lost my balance.

A dark mass emerged out onto the path just behind us. It was fairly large, about the size of a husky. I think it was the thing that had fled back towards the warehouse. It had come back.

It leapt towards Trinket. I use that description loosely: this thing didn’t have legs, or arms, or any limbs as I could see. It was this amorphous, black shape. It was pure darkness, black even against the darkness around us. It moved almost like a fluid, stretching out from one point in an arc, and as the front touched the ground, the rear part compressed forward until it was one blob-like mass again. But it was fast, just so fucking fast.

It collided with Trinket. My god, the way she shrieked as it made contact with her, the sound piercing my ears, it was horrible. She whined and screamed and snapped at it, but this fucking thing was, I think, trying to consume her.

And suddenly I was consumed with this pure, white-hot rage. I was still scared, terrified even. I had no idea what this thing was. Had we just crossed into its feeding ground? Had it killed and eaten these people whose remains we had found? I had no idea. But what I knew, in that moment, is that it was hurting my dog.

“Get the fuck off her!” I screamed at it, and I lunged forward. I punched downwards at it, my fist sinking into the soft mass, followed by a sharp stabbing pain across the skin of my right hand. It felt like thin needles pressing into my skin, razor sharp shards pushing under the flesh and grazing bone. I pulled back, my hand raw, skin already cracked and bleeding in a dozen places. The thing hadn’t let go of Trinket.

I plunged my fingers into this black mass. It felt weirdly like thick treacle.

And then pain. All over my hand, my fingers, just sheer utter agony. It was like thousands of burning needles stabbing into my flesh. I could feel those tendrils pressing under my skin again, tearing, tugging, pushing and writhing. With an awful grinding sensation, they pushed further and further, up the flesh of my hand, over my wrist. I could see squirming shapes under the skin, climbing, crawling, the entire time feeling that same tugging pull as it began eating my arm from the inside out.

I screamed, trying to grab onto something in this mass to get it off Trinket. I felt something small, but solid, like a rock in the middle of this liquid horror. Through the pain, I fought to get some control over my now-ruined hand, exerting every ounce of willpower I had. I clenched my fingers around the stone and yanked backwards, hard.

With a disgusting squelching sound, the mass released Trinket, and began to flow up my arm towards my shoulder. Whatever this creature was, the rock in my hand must have been its core. Gasping, I drew my arm back. Feeling the stone in my hand, burning hot, I threw it has hard as I could.

Have you ever heard someone trying to pull their leg out of a puddle of mud, that deep, wet sucking sound as the air fills the vacuum between the water, mud and limb as it escapes? That’s as close as I can describe the sound this thing made as it flew off my hand. With a splash, it landed in the canal, and was gone.

I was breathing hard. My heart was pumping, my head was pounding, my arm was throbbing under the fire of screaming nerve endings. I moved my hand up in front of my face to check the damage.

My skin was shredded and torn in dozens of places, flaps of skin and flesh hanging loose, blood oozing from the wounds and dripping from my hand. A couple of my fingernails were missing, and I could barely move my fingers. A whimper to my left brought my attention back to Trinket.

She was standing there, tongue out, ears back. Some of the fur on her front left leg was missing, and there were a couple of small open wounds that looked raw. She limped over to me and whimpered, but she seemed ok. That was the important thing. My darling little girl was ok.

The walk back home was uneventful, but I was on edge the entire time. Every sound, every rustle of a tree or bush made me look around nervously. I was feeling lightheaded and woozy, all too aware of the bleeding ruin of my arm.

We got to the front door of the house. I was shaking and feeling very weak. I fumbled for the keys in my pocket, and unlocked the door. As I opened the door and stepped in, Laura was just coming down the stairs to greet us.

“Hi honey, how was your – oh my God, what happened?”

I briefly explained to Laura what had happened. I was wobbling on my feet, and leaned against the wall for support, leaving a wet, red stain on the white paint.

Laura grabbed her car keys, and helped me out of the door and into the car. She had to help Trinket into the back seat too.

As we drove to the hospital, Laura called the police to warn them of the ‘dangerous animal’ that had attacked her husband and dog. I was only dimly aware of the conversation over the speaker-phone, as I was busy trying not to fall asleep and keep the towel wrapped tight around my bleeding hand. I do remember that, as soon as Laura told them about my injuries and what I had said the thing looked like, the line clicked, and the young woman she had been speaking to was replaced by a gruff, stern sounding man.

I don’t recall what was said, I must have drifted off. I was jolted awake when we arrived at the hospital. Laura helped me inside, but we had to leave Trinket in the car. Her wounds had stopped bleeding, and her ears were perked back up, so she seemed fine.

I was taken to a private room. There were two police officers stood by either side of the door as I was wheeled in, but they didn’t even glance at me.

I was examined by a couple of doctors. Over half of the skin had been taken off my right hand, and there was damage to the muscle and tendons in my fingers. There was some nerve damage, too. I was told I would lose some of the mobility in my hand, but once the skin and flesh had healed, they could look at physiotherapy to establish what my range of motion would be and help restore movement.

I was kept in the hospital for a couple of days. They ran multiple blood tests, took x-rays, I even went in for an EEG. I don’t know why they needed to do that for a hand injury, but I guess the doctors know best.

The police interviewed me a couple of times while I was recovering. They asked me the same questions each time: Where I had been walking? Was anyone else there at the time of the incident? What did the animal look like again? What colour was it? Had I been drinking that evening? And every time, I would tell them the same things: I was walking along the canal and we passed the old warehouse. There was no-one else on the path at any time during my walk. It wasn’t an animal, it was some black mass of living liquid. Yes, I said black, like purest darkness. No, I hadn’t been fucking drinking. Sorry officer, it’s just the pain is making me short tempered, I apologise for swearing at you.

Their official statement is I was attacked by a badger. A fucking badger. What a joke. Badgers aren’t made of living nightmare, they don’t ooze their way up your arm and under your skin and tear your flesh out from the inside while trying to eat you alive. And that’s another thing, the police told me they didn’t find any bones or blood or anything else that would suggest anyone else had been attacked. I find that hard to believe.

I was released yesterday. Laura came and picked me up from the hospital. She visited me every day, but also had to take care of Trinket and keep going to work. Can you believe that, they wouldn’t let her take any additional ‘compassionate leave’ to spend time with her injured husband? Dicks.

Trinket greeted my as soon as we got home. She came bounding out of the kitchen, tail wagging and ears perked up, like usual, but when she jumped up to me, she seemed to pause. Her ears went back and she whimpered, then ran off into the living room.

“She hasn’t seen you for a few days, honey,” Laura said comfortingly. “And she’s never seen you with your arm bandaged like that. She’s just being moody.”

It took Trinket a couple of hours to finally sit on the sofa next to me. She usually will jump onto the seat next to me and lay her head on my lap, but when she sat next to me, she just kind of stared at me. When I went to pet her, she recoiled at first, but then let me stroke her head. She’s being really nervous around me.

As much as that does bother me, the worst thing is the coughing. Last night my shoulder was aching, a deep, dull throb that spread into my collarbone and chest. Since I woke up this morning, every couple of hours, I can feel a sharp pain in my chest, almost like there’s a small bubble between my lungs and ribs. I’ll start coughing for a few minutes, and I struggle to catch my breath before it passes. But the last coughing fit was the worst, and my lungs felt like they were on fire. It felt like there was some phlegm stuck in my throat as I coughed. I ran into the bathroom, and finally managed to cough it up.

A small, black blob was writhing in the sink.

I could have died in a school shooting by MrHavoc415

I remember this day like yesterday and although I wasn't there, it feels like I was. It traumatizes me to this day.

Here's some context: This happened when I was 16, Im 20 now. I was that type of kid that didn't really care about my education. I was typically tardy and absent.

It was a Sunday night and I was debating wether or not I wanted to go to school the next day. I ended up coming to this consensus with myself that I would go, it was a Monday and we all hate Mondays but I would go just to get it out of the way. However, that Monday morning, I woke up with a nasty headache and didn't feel like getting out of bed. I told my parents how I felt and they said that I could stay home but I would have to go the next day. So that morning I stayed in bed trying to get some rest. I ended up taking a couple of aspirins to ease that terrible headache.

At about 9:15 I get this text from my friend. We're super close and had about 3 classes together. So anyway, he messages me saying "Bro, you'll never believe what happened. We're in a lockdown right now. Apparently someone was seen with a gun on campus." I replied with a "holy shit, that's insane. Do they know who it is?". He hit me back with "nah, not yet. Everyone here is going crazy tho, they're telling us not to panic but there's a psycho with a gun over here." "Well keep me posted then" I answered. I headed back to bed, but couldn't sleep. Thinking about that situation had me on edge.

I finally passed out and woke up to the vibration of my phone. I read it and my blood ran cold. "Holy shit man some classrooms got shot up and some people are seriously hurt, I haven't heard who specifically yet but fuck, and the guy who did it, holy fuck you wont believe it." I replied with "damn, who did it? Which classes did they shoot?" I remember shaking uncontrollably as I read the messages. "Mr fucking Tucker did it, and holy fuck the h classes were hit, apparently some kids died, Don't you have classes over there? Shit Im losing my mind man".

I was so confused, Mr. Tucker, the teacher that was fired the previous week. I then received the next message "The cops were in a shootout with Tucker, he shot some cops too. He's dead now". Well apparently a couple weekends ago, a student saw Mr. Tucker dealing drugs and took a video of it. The student showed the principal the next week and he was fired. I never had Mr. Tucker but he seemed like a laid back guy and he never appeared to be drugged up. He had a breakdown when he was told he was fired and left angry, cussing out the rest of the staff. I turned on the news to see this incident being the highlight, a helicopter cam capturing the crime scene.

They didn't announce who was injured, who was dead, etc. They evacuated shortly after and the school was closed for several weeks after. I remember two days had past before they announced the victims. As I saw who they were announcing, I started tearing up, I started shaking uncontrollably. I felt so, so sad for the kids and their families. I noticed some of the victims were kids in the same class I had. Geometry, second period. I came to the realization that I could have been there, I could have died that day. If it wasn't for that headache, I could have shared the same fate as my classmates, God rest their souls. To this day, that event makes me appreciate life a little more, it's terrifying.

I have always had Epilepsy. Please help! by Heavenli

So when I woke up, in the morning 2 days ago I felt the same as any other day. I didn’t want to move out of my lovely bed and snoozed as much as I could get away with. I could feel my partners warm body next to me and I just wanted to stay in bed with him but unfortunately I have to work for a living so I peeled myself out of bed.

I got straight up and went into the bathroom to take a shower and noticed a bottle of shampoo and conditioner on the shelf that I do not use. Now I’m vegan and only use certain products and these were ones that were a big no no. However I was still half asleep so didn’t think too much of it. I got in the shower and when I got out, and felt more refreshed, I started noticing other little differences.

I was sure the toilet roll holder was on the wrong side of the toilet and my toothbrush was red instead of green. A wooden shelf which holds most of my toiletries was replaced by a mental wire one. I still kind of thought I was just half dreaming still and decided the best thing would be to just get out of the bathroom and make some coffee.

However, I was not prepared for the shock that was to come. As I walked out of the bathroom I could see my partners body shape in the bed with his head sticking out faced away from me. My partner is half Turkish and has dark hair and eyes and olive skin. This man, in my bed, had a mop of blonde hair. I closed my eyes and counted to ten and opened them again and the blonde haired man was still in my bed.

I then heard a voice shouting Mum and a little girl came into the room I guessed at the time she was about 4. She came and grabbed my hand and asked me to make breakfast. God knows how I looked as I was so dumbfounded. I said “sweetie who are you and what are you doing here”. She replied “Stop being silly mummy” and she pulled my hand and i walked downstairs with her.

The house downstairs was pretty much identical to my own house, that I knew, but I did notice the subtle differences. In the living room the tv was at the opposite side of the room and there was a coffee table in the middle of the room I had never seen before. In the kitchen there was no coffee machine, just a kettle, and the microwave and toaster were red instead of blue. I also looked down when I heard a little noise and realised it was a cat rubbing itself around my legs Meowing.

Now I love all animals but I have never owned a cat. I have a dog named Sampson who is a pit bull cross and 15 years old. As I had cancer at a young age I couldn’t have children so Sampson was my child and I loved him like one. So this cat rubbing around my legs only confused me further.

This small child who kept calling me mummy asked me to make her breakfast and asked if we were still going to the beach today. I told her that I have to go to work,as I didn’t know what else to say, and at that point I was still in shock. She laughed and said “Silly mummy you don’t work anymore because Daddy has a really good job so you get to spend more time with me”.It was then I heard heavy feet coming down the stairs and the blonde haired stranger came into the kitchen.

He said “Hey my two beautiful girls, are we ready for the beach today”. I couldn’t speak I felt frozen like I was incapable of speaking or moving. I remember him saying oh my god honey are you ok and then it all went black.

I woke up in hospital dazed and confused and saw a nurse at the side of me checking my blood pressure. She hadnt realised I had woken up and after a few seconds I felt a smile form. I realised then I must have been dreaming during a seizure or something and the blonde man and the child didn’t exist and I wasn’t going crazy.

For as long as I can remember I have always had epilepsy but hadn’t had a seizure for about 3 years so it was odd but not a complete surprise. The nurse realised I was awake and she asked how I was feeling. She said” I will let your husband in to see you now”. I went to say hes not my husband yet when around the curtain in walked blonde guy and the little girl. I found out blonde guy was named James and we had apparently been together for 7 years and had our daughter Ellie 5 years ago. We had met online and fell in love instantly. I managed to find all of this by feigning memory loss just to get the information quickly.

James started saying how worried he was when he saw the seizure and he thought I was going to die and he hadn’t know what it was. I told him that although I hadn’t had a seizure for a while Epilepsy doesn’t ever really go away but then I found out, of course, apparently I don’t even have Epilepsy and I am not on treatment for it.

I had enough then and I broke down in tears and blurted all of it out. How I didn’t know him, that I’m not married, don’t have children and do have Epilepsy. I got into such a state that a nurse came running in and asked James to leave and Ellie was also getting very upset.

The nurse went out quickly and came back in with a glass of water. She said “James” had shown her pictures of me and him together to prove he was my husband. She said it was probably because of the seizure my memories were muddled and I was going to be sent for a head scan and then a dr would see me.

I had the scan and about an hour after the dr came to see me. There was no sign of James and Ellie which I was glad of. The dr diagnosed me with Temporal lobe epilepsy which I already knew I had. I tried to tell the dr this and tried to tell him that when I woke up this morning everything, including my husband, was different and that I could not have children as I had cancer young.

He went out and came back in and in a grave face told me he had reviewed my medical records and I had never had cancer nor been diagnosed with Epilepsy. I was to stay in hospital for observation and the he said within a few days my memory should be back to how it was.

The next day James came to see minus Ellie and said she had found it all too upsetting. I stuck by what I had said and he was upset but still stuck by the belief it was due to the seizure. As my memory was still off I stayed in another night. Earlier today James came to see me again and brought my phone. He told me to look through all the pictures and videos of us together and then he left. I did look and there was our wedding pictures, me pregnant with Ellie and pictures of holidays abroad.

I’m still in the hospital and have been told the dr wants to keep me in another night. I’m so frightened I don’t know what to do. I tried phoning my best friend but her phone was out of service and I don’t recognise any of the names in my phone. One is under the name Mum which I can’t bring myself to ring as my mum died 7 years ago. If anyone has any suggestions of what may be happening to me it would be much appreciated. I have no clue what to think but know I’m not crazy.

I love my wife. by capuslizn

The day I met Janette was the best day of my entire life. Second only to the day I married her.

I’ll never forget how pristine she looked walking down the aisle towards me. Her dress a blinding white complementing her porcelain skin perfectly. Her dark hair resting in beautiful curls held in place by pearl-decorated pins. I’ll never forget how fragile the veil felt in my fingers as I lifted it from her face to kiss her.

That’s my wife. My charming, beautiful, witty, wife.

We dated for four years before I finally asked her to wed me. Our relationship was perfect. We shared similar interests, and those we didn’t, the other quickly grew to love. She was truly my other half. The yin to my yang, the light to my darkness. My one and only.

Her family loved me, and my family loved her. Our wedding preparations went by so quickly it barely felt like it happened at all. First, we were two big-eyed kids in love with each other, and then suddenly we were married in a beautiful house of our own.

It was a dream. The relationship everyone pines for, we had it. And with barely any effort at all. Just me and Janette against the world.

Two years after we tied the knot, Janette became pregnant. Children were never in our plans, but you know what they say. Nothing’s 100% effective.

She was glowing as her belly swelled up, she was the epitome of motherly beauty and she hadn’t even had our child yet. But she was deeply in love with it. She talked to it all the time, and convinced me to do the same, but it never felt right.

Of course, she was my beautiful darling Janette, I would do anything for her. The thought of throwing away our rambunctious life of travel and young-love wasn’t even a thought when I saw how happy stroking her stomach made her look. Even after all these years, even a smile from her was enough to floor me.

That’s my wife. I love her so much more than anyone could know.

I tried so hard to be a good father. When the child came, a beautiful baby girl; Abigail, I helped Janette out as much as I could. The birth had done a number on her physically, so I took charge and pampered her as I cared for our daughter.

They always tell you how newborns scream, but they never convey how sharp the sound is.

“One more person to join our love-fest.” Janette would joke, kissing Abigail on top of her bald little head. I hated when she said that. But I loved her so much. Anything she loved, I would grow to.

I did a lot of research when Abigail came, I wanted to be prepared. I wanted to be the dedicated and loving husband Janette expected me to be. I would do anything for her.

Abigail was cute, and she smelled amazing, and she gurgled in the most perfect way if you tickled her cheeks. But she screamed so loudly in the night I feared for my life sometimes when she woke me.

Janette would just smile with tired eyes. “It’s fine, Tom. I’d do anything for her. Even wake up every ten minutes at 2am.”

I remember when she'd say the same to me, when I'd surprise her in the early hours of the morning to make love. But Janette loved her so dearly, so I tried to as well.

In my research I learned about SIDS. A truly terrifying condition that would take infants for seemingly no reason whatsoever, often due to difficulty breathing properly.

When Abigail fell victim to it, Janette tore herself apart. She was inconsolable. I took care of her for months after that, being the pillar she could lean on in this time of grief. It was the saddest I’ve ever seen her, and I knew I never wanted to see it again. Our love was the only thing that held her upright while she grieved, as I knew it would. I did the best I could for her. After all, I love my wife.

I resolved to get a vasectomy, so we would never be faced with such a horrible situation ever again. Janette was okay with it, as much as it pained her to think of children at all anymore. Children were never in our plans of course, and if one were to come again like Abigail, I don’t think I’d be able to do it. I love Janette too much to hurt her again. I would die for that woman. I would kill for that woman.

I recently bought a mansion in Vermont by ItadakiYT

I’ve always been one fortunate guy. My dad was the CEO of a large meat company, making me the spoiled son of a millionaire. I finished college a month back, graduating with barely passing grades due to a lot of partying so I decided it was time to settle down for a comfortable life. I bought a mansion in Vermont, a fairly old stone brick structure in the middle of a large forested area about half a mile from the city. Since then, some rather odd things happened to me during my first year of living there. Below are excerpts from the log I keep, describing the strange events.

A week after I moved in, I had a party with a bunch of my friends. We wanted to turn on the fountain in the front of the house, so I went down to the basement to find the switch. The basement was a cool and damp place and all the lights were dead. I brought a flashlight but the battery ran out halfway to my surprise, I changed the batteries a day ago so I wasn’t sure why. I found the switch for the fountain and ran up the stairs. Turns out the fountain didn’t work because it was clogged with “coagulated green slime”. The plumber told me it was probably rotting algae. The plumber also disappeared the night he was repairing the fountain.

I got lost on the third floor today. After leaving the bathroom from throwing up from last night’s drink, I found myself in a less familiar hallway. I opened the door across the hall and found myself peering down a dark stairwell. I could hear something dripping from the bottom. I tried many other doors and they led to strange rooms, colored red, green, blue, as if they were children’s rooms. One room led to an indoor garden. I never saw these rooms before, so I came to the conclusion that I was still drunk. I wasn’t.

Someone has been breathing down my neck all day today. At least that’s what it feels like. I’ve closed all the windows because I thought it may have been drafts of wind today, even though the weather was perfectly still. It still continued, even when I was lying in bed that night.

I feel like food has been missing from my refrigerator lately. Numerous steaks and my salami has gone missing over the span of one week. I checked around the house to see if I had misplaced them while I was drunk but I stopped because I felt like I was being followed. Trails of warm putrid smelling liquid also covered my floors one evening. I wiped them down with paper towels but the stench was burning my nostrils. I felt like it was melting my flesh because of the smell. It was melting the paper towels however, I had to use a whole roll to clean it completely. I think there’s a stray dog or raccoon in my house eating my food. I would call an exterminator but I think I can handle it by myself.

I’ll continue updating my list of occurrences and maybe later post them if they continue to bother me. I’ve asked many people if they know what’s going on but no one seems to have the same experiences as mine. The previous owners wouldn’t respond to my emails too. They sent me one email and one only, saying “Please Leave.”

Last jewelry heist went very wrong – need help by JeffreyFMiller

Jeff isn’t my real name, and none of the other names are, either. You’ll see why. Usually, I keep my mouth shut tight about my work, but I’m stuck in something way out of my depth and need help. If any of you can tell me how to get out this alive and in one piece, I’d be greatly in your debt. Here’s the situation.

I hadn’t had a job in a little over a month. My last score had actually been pretty good, but I’d paid for too many rounds and hadn’t had the best luck at craps. I was down to my last five hundred bucks, so a couple of weeks ago, I quietly started getting the word out that I was available to work again.

I’m not a heavy. I don’t carry a gun, and I don’t rough people up. I’m a safecracker. I used to be an honest locksmith years ago, but that’s a 50-hour-a-week drudge. Nowadays, I put in eight or nine hours on a job, and the rest of the month is mine.

Anyway, last week, I was enjoying a pint with a few of the boys at an Irish pub downtown. Ben, the bartender, gave me a look when he poured my second pint, and I knew what that meant. I excused myself to go to the bathroom, and saw that Ben was already in the back alley.

“How badly do you want to work?” he asked.

I shrugged. “I could use a job. What’s the problem?”

“There’s a guy I know. Friend of a friend. I can’t vouch for him personally, and, to be honest, he’s weird. But my friend says he’s solid. Always pays well. Jobs go off without a hitch.”

“Weird how?”

Ben looked away from me and pursed his lips. He shook his head. “I don’t know. He just gives me the heebie-jeebies.”

“Really?” I smirked. “The heebie-jeebies?”

“Hey, fuck you. See for yourself. He’s looking for a good safecracker, and he’s sitting in the corner alone. Orange hoodie. Can’t miss him. If it goes bad, don’t blame me. I warned you.”

He opened the door to the bar. “And I’d better get my finder’s fee.” Ben shut the door, hard.

Just as Ben said, he was hard to miss. Bright orange hoodie, dirty jeans, and a Tampa Bay Buccaneers baseball cap. He was chubby, and wore an ugly class ring with a false ruby on his left hand. I sat down.

“You’re the guy, huh?” he said.

“Ben said you need a locksmith.”

“That I do. He said you’re skilled, you keep your mouth shut, and you follow directions. Is that right?”

I was beginning to understand what Ben meant. I couldn’t tell you why I felt the way I did, but the more he spoke, the more I felt my skin crawl.

“That’s right. What have you got in mind?”

“Let’s take a walk.”

I did not want to be alone with this guy. But I also knew that I was going to run out of money in about a week, and I didn’t have any other prospects. So, I stood up and left the bar with him, shooting a look at my buddies to come look for me if I wasn’t back soon. We walked down a nearly deserted side street, and he gave me the details.

It was crazy. The joint he had in mind was a jewelry store downtown. I knew it. Nothing too pricy, but they didn’t sell zircons, either. He wanted me to put a black bag over my head and walk inside during business hours. A black bag with no eyeholes. He said that once I was inside, he’d tell me the rest.

“This is your plan?” I said, quietly. “You and Ben can go fuck yourselves. I’m a professional, and I don’t put up with practical jokes.”

He gave me a shit-eating grin while he reached into the pocket of his hoodie. For a second, I thought he was going to knife me, so I backed away. But it was just a lighter.

Then he was gone. Vanished.

A light tap on my shoulder nearly made me cry out. It was him. Behind me.

“You need me to show you anything else? I’m not sure you’d like it, but I can be more impressive if you still need convincing.”

I was too rattled to do anything but shake my head.

“Tomorrow at noon, then. The park across the street from the store?”

I stammered a yes.

“Good. I’ll bring the bag. You bring your tools. You’ll like the split.” And he named a figure so large it just about made me choke.

He continued down the street, while I doubled back for another round of beers. I gave Ben a wad of cash for his trouble.

“What the fuck did you get me into, Ben?”

He just shrugged and went back to polishing pint glasses.

The next morning, I examined and cleaned my tools, though they didn’t really need cleaning, and triple checked that I had everything I’d need. Satisfied, I put on my lucky shirt, a genuine Sandy Koufax jersey from his 1965 season. Years ago, we hit some rich douchebag who was into sports memorabilia, and I took it as part of my share. It hasn’t failed me yet. I put a jacket on over the jersey, grabbed my tools and left to go meet Mr. Black Bag.

He was sitting on a bench in a small park cattycorner from the jewelry store, wearing the same clothes as the day before. I sat down next to him and opened a newspaper I’d bought on the way over. For a few minutes, we said nothing. Then, he placed a large black bag and an old-fashioned key beside him. Without looking at me, he began to speak.

“I’m going to get up and go into the store,” he said, calmly and deliberately. “When I enter, count to 20, walk briskly to the entrance, and pull the bag over your head. Bring the key. I’ll direct you verbally to the safe when you’re inside.”

With that, he got up and crossed the street, as casually as a man going out for coffee and a bun.

I didn’t see him put on a mask before he entered, which worried me, because I knew there were guards and cameras inside. A couple of years ago, I’d cased this place myself, and security was tight. Without someone on the inside, we didn’t see how it could work, so we abandoned the idea.

I started counting. Every bone in my body wanted to ditch this job, but Ben had vouched for this creep, mostly, and he’d never steered me wrong before. Besides, if I left, my reputation would be trashed, and it wasn’t out of the question I’d get two behind the ear. And with this head case? Maybe worse than that. In any case, I didn’t hear any alarms or commotion, and it was too late to pull out now.

I reached twenty, took a deep breath and crossed the street. I glanced furtively to my left and right. It didn’t seem that anyone was paying attention to me, so I pulled the bag over my head – it was made of rough cotton and smelled like old socks – and slipped inside.

The store was deathly silent. I could feel the presence of other people, but they didn’t seem to be moving and certainly weren’t making any noise. I’m not even sure they were breathing, but that might be because my own breath was so loud inside the bag. It was hot, and the rough fabric I felt gooseflesh rising on my arms and neck.

“Four steps forward, turn to your right 90 degrees, and straight ahead for 12 more paces. That will bring you to the counter. Take your time. There’s no hurry.”

I tried not to piss myself and cautiously did as he said. I hated walking blind, but his directions were good. I could feel the gate that led behind the counter.

“Open it. Three paces forward and you’ll be at the door to the back office. It will be empty. Close the door behind you, and remove the bag. You’ll see the safe. Make sure the key is touching your skin the entire time while you open it.”

As I opened the gate and walked to the door, he continued to give instructions.

“Take only the purple sack, and close the safe back up. Do not open the sack. Make sure you do not open the door or even look through the window to the showroom without the bag covering your head again.”

As soon as I closed the office door behind me, I took that god-awful bag off my head and took a deep breath of clean air.

The office was small and sparsely furnished. A wooden desk with a landline phone, a floor lamp that was turned on, and a bookshelf packed with gemology references decades out of date.

Plus, a safe. A large top-of-the-line safe.

I couldn’t crack a safe with one hand, so I shoved the key into my sock. Crazy, I know, but with this guy, I wasn’t going to take any chances. Not yet, anyway. Someone had doodled all around the dial with a permanent marker, which was strange, but it was easier to open than I’d expected. It took just ten minutes. The safe didn’t make a sound as I opened it.

For a moment, I couldn’t do anything but stare. I’d expected to see jewelry, cash, loose stones, maybe even drugs or a few guns. But there wasn’t any of that.

The safe was full of junk. I didn’t look through it all, but what I saw made me uneasy: Monopoly pieces carved out of bone, sepia prints of children with their mouths open far too wide, what looked like an Elvis Presley death mask, a stack of quarters with Washington’s eyes scratched out ... you get the idea. The worst, though? The worst was a pile of crayon drawings of the 9/11 attacks. Even though they were clearly done by kindergartners, they felt more vivid and horrible than actual photos from the scene.

After a couple of minutes of searching, I found it: a purple Crown Royal sack with the cords cinched shut. I closed the safe and glanced toward the door. It was on the right-hand wall, so I couldn’t see into the showroom, but a sickly glow shone in through the window in the door. It made me feel lightheaded.

Maybe it was the light that made me do it, or maybe I just wanted to see how far this freak show went. Either way, I know what gemstones feel like, and this sack wasn’t filled with jewels.

“Fuck it,” I said and sat down at the desk to open the sack.

I can still hardly believe what was inside. The sack was full of colorless glass marbles, and each one contained the roughly sawed-off head of an action figure: GI Joe, My Little Pony, Star Wars and a bunch of others I didn’t recognize.

I couldn’t imagine he was going to all this trouble for flea-market garbage, so I looked closer, figuring this had to be some kind of a scheme for smuggling. Maybe the marbles melted down into drugs? Or were some kind of explosive? Some kind of spy shit, maybe?

That’s when I started and almost tipped over the desk chair. Every single one of those sawed-off doll heads was facing up. I’d swear I’d seen those heads turn to stare directly at me.

I closed the sack, went to the door, and pulled the black bag over my head, my heart pounding. When I entered the showroom, the guy asked if I’d gotten it, and I nodded. He directed me to the front door, and told me to remove the black bag without turning around. He’d meet me in the park shortly.

Five minutes after I sat down on the bench, he joined me.

“You got it?”

I handed him the Crown Royal sack, the black bag and the key.

“You didn’t open it, did you?”

“Of course not. When do I get my end?”

“Right now,” and he handed me a manila envelope stuffed with enough cash to last me at least six months. I couldn’t believe he’d do this out in public, but no one paid us any mind. I stashed it in my tool bag.

“You did well. If I need you again, I’ll let Ben know.”

And with that, he stood up and walked away.

It was nearly 12:30 pm, and I needed a beer and a burger. Several beers, actually. On my way out of the park, I glanced back at the jewelry store. Customers were going in and out of the front door as if nothing had happened.

I sat down at my favorite bar and grill and tried to catch the bartender’s attention, but she was with another customer. I dug in my pocket to find my phone while I waited.

Instead of pulling out my phone, though, I pulled out one of those marbles. Embedded in its center was the head of some weird Japanese manga character. Huge eyes with a little grin on its face. I couldn’t tell if it was a boy or a girl.

I knew I had left every one of those marbles in the sack. I’d never even picked any up. I stepped outside, dropped it down a sewer gate, and took my seat again, wiping the cold sweat off my forehead.

The bartender was standing directly in front of me.

“You look nervous, honey. Something wrong?”

“Just hungry. Probably coming down with something. Give me a burger and whatever’s good on tap.”

She didn’t move.

“What are you looking at? I said a burger and a beer.”

She smiled, and said, “What’s your name again?”

“Jane, I’ve been in here twice a week for years. What kind of game are you playing?”

“Just feeling flirty,” she said, not flirty at all.

I ate the burger and drank the beer, but everything had felt so wrong today, including Jane, I decided to skip a second beer and go home. I had beer in my fridge.

When Jane brought the tab, I laid down a twenty, and she glared at me.

“Not paying with a card?”

“Jane, what the fuck? I always pay cash. What do you care?”

Her face turned mean, and she grabbed my wrist with a strength I didn’t expect.

“Why did you steal from me?’ she hissed, so close to my face, I could feel the spittle hitting my cheeks. “You do not want me to visit you in person. Give me your name.”

I broke away and ran out into the street, knocking down an old man with a cane. I apologized, profusely, and helped steady him with my arm. But as I brought him to his feet, he grabbed my neck, choking me.

“Who hired you? I will have the flesh chewed off your bones if you do not tell me. I couldn’t see your master, but I know someone with power was there.”

I kneed the old man in the groin, and he doubled over in pain. People on the sidewalk gasped. One young guy tried to be a hero, chasing after me, but I’ve been chased before and lost him after a couple of blocks. Thankfully, we didn’t run into any cops. I chalked that up to my lucky jersey.

I had a nasty bruise on my neck and didn’t want to see anyone else at this point, so I took back alleys and crossed a vacant lot to my building. When I reached my floor, my mobile started ringing. I stepped inside my apartment and answered. It was Ben.

“That guy called. He sounds pissed off. The fuck did you do?”

“I did the job. He paid me. It’s done.”

“Well, he’s shitting a brick. Said that you’d better call him or he’d take it out on me. Call him. Now.”

Ben gave me a number and hung up before I could say anything more.

What could I do? I called him.

“You looked, you idiot. You opened the bag! There’s only 39 marbles, and there’s supposed to be 40. Do you have any idea what you’ve done?”

“Marbles? What are you talking about? I didn’t look. It was none of my business.”

“You’re a terrible liar. Look, we can work this out. Tell me where you live and what it looks like.”

“What do you mean what it …”

“The face. Tell me what the face in the marble looks like. Give me your address, and I can take care of it.”

“Are you crazy? A face? What the hell did you have me steal?”

He went quiet for a moment. When he spoke again, it was in a different tone. Friendly, almost.

“Ok, fine. Maybe there were just 39 in the sack. Tell me what else was in the safe.”

I was a little shaken by the sudden change of tone, but I started to tell him anyway. The Monopoly pieces, the mask, the photos, the drawings … and then I shut up, because I suddenly knew what he was up to.

That weirdo was tracing my location. I opened the back of my mobile and removed the battery.

I was just thinking what a chore it would be to circulate a new number when I heard, “C’mon my lovely little locksmith. Did you think you’d get rid of me that easily? It’ll be easier for you if you stay put.”

The battery was in my right hand and the phone was in my left, but he was still talking to me through the device. Without hesitation, I opened the window and dropped both of them four stories to the concrete. I didn’t wait to see them smash before I started packing a bag.

As I packed, I noticed a bulge in the outer pocket of my suitcase. Thinking I might have forgotten some toiletries from my last trip, I unzipped it up and reached inside. It wasn’t soap or a mini-bottle of shampoo. It was the marble. Again.

As I held it, those huge manga eyes turned slowly in their non-existent sockets to stare at me. It was no longer smiling.

I got a mallet and pounded the marble on a cutting board until it shattered. I flushed the glass down the toilet and melted the plastic head in a cast iron pan. It smelled horrible. As I jogged to my car, I tossed the pan in a sidewalk garbage can.

Ten hours later, I was in a room at a Motel 6 in the middle of nowhere, playing solitaire on a wobbly desk in the corner. The TV was on, but I wasn’t watching. I just wanted the white noise.

I heard something clank and looked up. The door latch had flipped open, and the doorknob was turning. I stood up and grabbed the desk lamp. Not much of a weapon, but it’d have to do.

He walked inside, still wearing that hideous orange hoodie, and closed the door as if the room belonged to him. The television made a popping sound and went black. The overhead light faded to nothing. I felt my stomach drop and muttered curses under my breath.

“I’m sorry to do this. Really, I am. But you opened yourself up to her by opening that bag, and she can get to me through you. It won’t hurt, though. I promise you that. You won’t feel a thing.”

As he spoke, he removed things from his pockets. In his right fist, he held a lighter. In the other, a gnarled human hand with wicks coming out of each of the fingers and the thumb. They were melted halfway down. I don’t know how, but I was certain this wasn’t a replica. It was real or, at least, it had been, once.

As he lit it, a pale light painted the room the color of bile, growing stronger as each wick caught fire. Once his grisly candelabra was fully illuminated, he put the lighter away and, with a look of disgust on his face, drew a large knife. I stood, frozen.

He walked towards me, but stopped abruptly a couple of feet from where I stood, grimacing. He tried to walk forward again, but was stopped a second time, as if he’d run into a wall of glass. I think it was then he realized that the sickly light from his candle didn’t quite fill the room. It stopped at the edge of a circle made of sand.

You see, about nine hours earlier, I’d stopped at a McDonald’s off the highway for some coffee and decided to look through my old road atlas while I waited in line at the drive-thru. But instead of grabbing the atlas from the glove box, I brought back that same marble for a third time. The manga head looked like it was snarling at me, and I could see fangs in its mouth.

I wanted to cry, but after a minute of pounding on the steering wheel while screaming, I regained my composure and accepted that running was pointless. One of these two freaks would find me eventually.

When the garbled voice from the drive-thru speaker gave me one last chance to tell her who had hired me, the choice was simple. She wanted him, and he almost certainly wanted me dead. I came clean and made a deal with her.

She told me the words I needed, and I stopped at a Kmart to buy the materials. A 25-pound bag of play sand was all they had, but the Elmo doll on the endcap told me it would work just fine.

Continuing the circle under the bed and the other furniture was a pain in the ass, and I was terrified that he would break it when he entered the room, but he didn’t. Just as she instructed, I’d left the marble on the desk so she could find him.

He begged me to free him as I shimmied around the edge of the motel room, careful to stay outside the circle. As I climbed over the bed with my back against the wall, he pleaded with me not to leave him there for her, but I ignored him. I knew that even if he screamed, she’d make sure no one did anything before she arrived, and she’d said she’d clean up once she was finished. Nothing would be traced back to me. Besides, I was 100 percent certain he’d still kill me if I let him go.

This morning, I received a box in the mail, no return address. Inside was a bright orange hoodie that looked as if it had been half devoured by moth larvae. It was covered in rusty stains. I put on a pair of gloves and dropped the hoodie in the trash. I’ll burn it later.

Underneath were two more objects. The first was a waxy, severed hand with unburnt wicks sticking out of each digit. An ugly class ring burrowed deep into one of the fingers. I guess she couldn’t get it off.

The other was a handwritten note on flowered stationary. It smelled faintly of lilac.

“I’ll be in touch. We have so much work to do.”

Living alone for the first time by ColdWorldGotHotter

I recently just moved into an apartment, all alone for the first time. I’m still in the same big city, but a new area. I’ve been here for a few weeks and was a bit late on getting window blinds. The lack of privacy started to get to me so I finally made a trip to the store. They didn’t have any nice blinds that fit my 80 inch windows, so I didn’t want to buy expensive ugly ones if they would be temporary. I opted in for the cheapest but biggest ones I can find, 64 inches was the compromise. I wasn’t quite sure how the placement would work, but I ended up just leaving a huge 16 inch gap on top.

When was I installing the blinds, I noticed something about my window that was connected to the fire escape. It didn’t have a latch, so the widow could quite easily just be ‘pushed’ to fall inward (or pulled from the inside). The super in my building also removed the window guards because “they aren’t necessary if you don’t have kids.” Something I wanted to address but waited a little too long to do.

I’m a bit of a stoner, so one night when I got home from work and night class, I decided to have a little doobie before I went to sleep. I put some music on, started smoking on my bed until my eyes were too heavy to stay awake. Half way through the night I wake up from a horrible song, my Spotify shuffle went somewhere it didn’t belong. In the whim of doing so, I hear something.

It sounds like metal clacking, similar to the noise my bird makes in his case. I put my phone away and rested my head on the pillow, eyes closed. Suddenly the noise is getting louder, more constant, like it’s getting closer. My small little bird couldn’t make these noises even if he tried, especially without him actually chirping.

I feel a little paralyzed, not because I am scared, but because I have no idea what to do. This is my first moment in my home where I have to deal with it by myself, all alone. I can’t do it, my body feels heavy. My mind tries to be rational, maybe it’s someone outside working or moving around.

At this point the sound has stopped, I’m too scared to raise my head and look around, it can’t be anything. Suddenly I hear a tap, my heart freezes, my throat closed, I can’t breath, I think I’m about to shallow my tongue. I have no idea what that noise is, but it sounded personal. It sounded so real, it had to be for me.

Again, I hear the tap, this time it doesn’t take too long to be accompanied by another tap... then again tap.. I want to scream, I want to cry, I want to call my dad, I need to do something!

Almost like a complete shock from my mind to my body, I react too quickly and jerk my head up. I stare at my window, the blinds are see-through thanks to the street light right around my window. I see a figure, it’s someone kind of crotching all the way very low, I don’t know if he can see me.

Can he see me? Again my body is unable to move, stuck in the same position like I’m in a deer in headlights. I hear another tap, all of them being ever so lightly. My heart is racing, my brain is overheating, my body feels like it’s crampijg up. I start to think “one hard tap and that entire bottom piece of the window is coming down”.

Oh god why didn’t I call the super to come fix this, why did I procrastinate? Suddenly, the man stands up. The fire escape is lower than my window so even with his large body, his head doesn’t reach the top of my blinds. He turns around, starts to walk up the fire escape to the next floor.

I’m sweating at this point, my bed feels my grave. I couldn’t see his face but I saw the back of his head, completely covered in a beenie hat of some kind. It sounds like he moved to the next floor, what am I supposed to do?

Am I that much of a coward? Am I going to let this guy go to my neighbor? Is any of this even real? Before I could decide what to do, I heard a huge slap on my window. He hit it from the top, I could feel the vibration on every inch of my body.

The slap on the top window was so hard it forced my bottom window to fall inward. It smashed into my radiator underneath it, causing it to shatter into pieces. I was so frightened I screamed as loud as I ever did before. I screamed and I screamed. My eyes were closed and I was in the fetal position, completely gave myself up.

Suddenly I hear something I didn’t expect, large knocks on the door. I dont know whar came over me, but I felt like it was over. The help was here, back to reality. I run to my door and open it, it’s my next door neighbor. He sees the window broken, quickly calls 911 and stays with me until the cops arrive.

As we waited, he listened to my story and I could tell he didn’t believe me at all. Just explained it as “ah you don’t know thia building, it’s prewar, stuff like this always happens!” That’s all it was, just the window randomly falling on its own.

When the cops arrived, it was like I was simply reliving the same moment with my neighbor. They looked at me like I was just making up a crazy story to justify being so scared from a window breaking.

Except one cop, I could tell he was new on the force just by how long he looked compared to the two guys talking to me. Once everyone else finished up with me, that cop had me repeat the story one more time just for me. Suddenly he did something noone else, including myself, thought of doing.

He looked at the top piece of the window that was still in place. There was a huge hand print on the window.

Mommy Please by skiitzofranikk

I'm really beginning to worry about Jacob. He just hasn't been himself lately. He has started questioning my every move. Can a child so young really be so paranoid? Day in and day out it's question after question after question,

" Mommy, why is it so cold? Mommy, why do we eat the same thing every night? Mommy, how come the lights never work at night?"

And day in and day out I give him the same response,

"Mommy is doing her best darling, everything is going to be okay. Be thankful we are together. All we need is each other. Now and forever."

Then he looks at me with those beautiful baby blues and shines his cute little grin revealing his two missing front teeth and my heart just melts.

"I love you mommy."

And I love him too, more than anything in the whole world.

I've done the best I can do for him. Being a single mother is hard and I wouldn't wish it on anyone. He may not have every little thing he wants, but he has everything he needs, with me. I am what keeps him alive and I am what keeps him safe. Some people may disagree with my methods but Jacob Is MY son, MY responsibility. It's no one else's business. I wish people would just mind their own. If I'm not careful I could lose everything and it would be all their fault.

Just the other day we were having a perfectly nice time at the park and this little girl almost spoiled it all. She and Jacob were playing together and she had the audacity to ask him,

"Why are your clothes so dirty? And you smell really weird."

My poor boy looked so sad and confused. He ran to me crying.

"Mommy, please that girl is so mean. Can we just leave?"

"Of course baby."

I brushed his hair aside and kissed his forehead. I sent him on ahead of me, I had no choice, I had to take care of this little brat, and he didn't need to see it. I rolled up my sleeves and walked up right behind her and shoved her forward so she fell face first onto the ground. I leaned down and grabbed her hair, pulling her head up just enough so I could whisper into her ear,

"Don't you ever talk to Jacob like that again."

and let go. She looked around wildly and scrambled to her feet screaming and running toward the benches where all the other parents sat. Serves her right. No one ever came after me, not that I was particularly concerned that they would to begin with. That night I made sure to comfort Jacob and assure him she was just a mean little girl and that he should never listen to people like her. He nodded in agreement but i could still she the pain etched on his little face. He was still hurt. He would keep looking down at his clothing and grimacing. I wish it were easier for me to get him the things he desperately wanted. The next day I made the decision, I was going to do what I had to do. I have no money so there was only one other option. Not too far from our home there lived a boy about Jacob's age so while he was sleeping I decided to sneak away to the boy's house. Both parents have full time jobs and the boy is enrolled in school so the house was completely empty. It was no trouble for me to slip in, though I did have to break a window. While I searched through the dresser drawers and closet I thought about how I really should find a way to get Jacob in school, but I don't think I could be away from him for that long. It wasn't the nicest clothing I had ever seen, but it would have to do. Jacob was thrilled when I came through the door, it was like i brought home buried treasure, but it didn't last.

"Mommy, How come we can see the sky through the roof?"

I was gone too long. I din't feed him on time. He always starts to notice things I would rather keep hidden if I don't get him his special treats. Judge me if you must, but when you have a child you will do just about anything to keep them safe and happy. I wouldn't do this if I didn't think it was absolutely crucial for our survival.

Odd things have been happening, there's a man who has been around. We see him every time we go out. At first I thought it was all coincidence, but now I'm not so sure. Maybe I'm just being paranoid, but it really seems like he is following us. We always manage to lose him before we get home, but he seems so determined to find us, how can we dodge him forever? Who is he? Why is he so hell bent on me and my son? I caught him talking to Jacob once on the sidewalk the other day, and it seems he has only become more interested in us since then. Jacob was chattering away, like young boys tend to do. He's far too trusting but it's not his fault, they don't know any better at this age, ya know? When I approached Jacob turned to me excitedly and gave me that glorious smile,

"Mommy! This is Jeff! He's really nice! He said he wants to take me to get a burger! Doesn't that sound tasty?"

The man look fairly confused and maybe even a little upset when my son turned to me. I grabbed Jacob's hand and we rushed off in the opposite direction. I looked back over my should and the man looked more bewildered than he had before. I scoffed to myself. Why is he so surprised? What mother wouldn't pull their child away in such a manner from a complete stranger?

This was the beginning of the end for us. If I had known then I would have taken Jacob far, far away from here, but how could I have guessed this would be the result?

It was a normal night for us. Jacob and I were laying down discussing our hopes and our dreams when a blinding light approached our house and came through our door.

"Mommy! What's happening?!"

I will never forget the fear in his voice but it was nothing compared to the pure terror in his eyes as men dressed head to toe in white followed the man who had talked to Jacob with flash lights, into our house and took him away from me. I ran after them and watched as they placed him in the back of an ambulance and strapped him down to a gurney. My poor baby, he was crying now and my heart ached because i was powerless to do anything about it. They started him on some sort of IV substance, whatever it was it wasn't a good thing, not for me anyway. I can already feel myself beginning to fade away. I guess it's time to admit the truth to myself. I don't actually exist. Not really. Jacob's real mother abandoned him, the heartless witch. Jacob found me while he was wandering the forest all alone desperately trying to find any kind of food he could. There was one particular bush he liked that contained some unknown berry. I'm not so sure they were exactly healthy but I kept that too myself. In fact, I kept him steadily supplied with them. Jacob needed me and whatever they were these berries made me seem so real to him. He needed me, that's why I appeared. He needed a mother, so that's what I became. WE found a run down house in the forest and we survived. Damn the nosy parents at the park. Damn the Department of Child Services.. Damn them all straight to hell.

I don't expect anyone to understand, but Jacob and I are one in the same. We complete each other. Even now as I drift further and further into non existence as the IV re-hydrates his system and he becomes more aware of reality around him. My heart shatters because I know this is it. Still he attempts to reach for me and I hear him whisper,

"Don't go. Mommy please."

Tears flow down his face and then, as if i had never been there to begin with, I was gone..

My Best Friend Ellen by SetItToWumbo94

She was the most beautiful girl I’d ever seen. Elegant, shining brunette hair. Beautiful, light green eyes. Rosy cheeks, lush lips, smooth skin. The way her spotless white dress fell over her frame, the way she never stopped smiling when she saw me, the way she never spoke badly of me. She was perfect. Her name, was Ellen.

Not only was she perfect, she was my bestest and closest friend. We did everything together. We would have sleepovers, wake up and eat breakfast together, we would go to school together, play in class and at recess, ride the bus home, adventure in my backyard until dinner, and even take baths together! I was the happiest little girl in the whole wide world. Ellen was by my side through thick and thin. I loved her so much, and she loved me too. But my parents said our close relationship was becoming a problem.

They started telling me I couldn’t hang out with Ellen as often as I used to. We stopped having breakfast together. We stopped playing during class and at recess. No more riding the bus home together. No more baths together. No more sleepovers. I was only allowed to play with her after I got home until dinner time, and then I had to say goodnight. Ellen didn’t like that one bit. So, she would sneak over and we’d still have slumber parties anyway!

We would talk about everything! What I did that day, what I learned in class, what I ate for lunch, who I played with at recess, all of it! Sometimes, Ellen would want to talk about my parents though. She wasn’t very nice when she did that. She started to say mean things like they needed to go away so we could be together more. She would ask me how I would feel if they were gone. She would tell me she knew ways of making my parents disappear. Then she would ask me what I thought about running away, about living on our own and being the queens of our own lives. Normally I would tell her, “I don’t know.” But one night, she just made being a queen sound like so much fun, and I loved Ellen to death, so I told her I was ready.

I really enjoyed Ellen and I’s secret sleepovers. But one day, my parents came to wake me up a little early and found us together in bed. They were very, very mad. “No more!” They both said. They told me Ellen and I weren’t allowed to see each other anymore, and I couldn’t stop crying for a long, long time.

The next day, when I came home from school, Ellen was sitting at my kitchen table. She told me she missed me, and she was sad that I didn’t come looking for her. I told her that I wanted to, but couldn’t, because my parents would be very upset if I did. That made her angry. She told me enough was enough. We were best friends, and we deserved to be together, forever. I asked her what she meant, but she just told me to wait until tomorrow morning, and that everything would be okay.

When my parents got home, they found Ellen and yelled at me for playing with her. I told them that I came home and she was just there, but they didn’t believe me for a second. The whole time they screamed at me, Ellen just stared with the meanest scowl on her beautiful face. Before she was taken away, she told me, “Goodnight, my queen.”

The next morning, Ellen was sitting on my bed. I asked her what she was doing, and she told me, “Whatever I want, we’re both queens now!” She said I didn’t have to go to school because queens don’t do that, and I was so excited I started jumping up and down and dancing with her! I told her that we had to tell my parents the good news, but she said there was no need, that they already knew! When I asked her what she meant, she told me to go into their room and see for myself.

I was ecstatic that my day was starting off so well. First, I wake up to my best friend, then she tells me I’m a queen, and finally, a surprise! I hopped out of bed and ran over to my parent’s room. The door was closed, which is weird because mommy and daddy were usually up getting ready. I knocked and called out to them, but didn’t hear anything, so I opened the door and walked in.

Mommy and daddy were very cold and blue. Daddy was sitting up in bed with his mouth wide open and a big red line across his throat. His eyes and tongue were missing. He looked like he wanted to scream, but nothing was coming out. Mommy was in the bathroom, swinging back and forth from a rope tied tight around her neck. She had red cuts across her wrists, and her tongue was missing too. Her eyes looked so sad, like she was saying sorry. I could hear Ellen giggling happily from my room.

The police came to my house after I didn’t show up for school for a few days. They found Ellen and I playing tea party in the living room. After seeing my parents, they took me away and asked a whole lot of questions. For years and years, I was moved around from place to place, each time being introduced to a new person in a white coat who would ask me things and try to “help me.” They thought I was crazy for some reason. They just kept saying over and over, “Macy, please. Please understand. There’s no physical way that a doll could’ve done those things to your parents...”

My Wife And I Bought A House Using Sherlock Homes Realty by thegeneralg

My wife Emily and I recently moved to a house about an hour outside of Minneapolis. We had just gotten married a year ago and this was our first official house together. It was such a happy time for us. We bought the house from a real estate firm called Sherlock Homes. Their tagline was "We track down the best home for you!" Corny, I know.

I double checked their reviews on Yelp, the Better Business Bureau, all that good stuff. Since they came up with good reviews, I had no problem using them. Our realtor was a woman named Carla and she looked the part of a realtor.

She had immaculate blond hair, a pearl necklace, and was always dressed in a solid colored business suit. She even had the posh looking designer bag and watermarked business cards. Every time she met with us, Carla was professional, likeable and prepared. She even managed to find us a house right off the bat that we immediately liked.

It was on a lovely hill overlooking a pond. Beautiful colonial house, lush green backyard, and bright flowers popping up at odd intervals on the sidewalk. As soon as Emily walked up the driveway with me, I could feel her excitement. Giving my hand a quick squeeze as we walked through the entryway. Stepping inside, it just felt right for us. Some houses you walk into they feel off, like it still belonged to the previous owner. Not this one. It felt fresh and new. Like a blank canvas.

Emily fell in love with the place and I could see she had to have this house. Since I didn't exactly mind the place myself, I agreed that we should take it. We moved in this past November and it went pretty smooth. Within a month or two, we had properly settled ourselves in.

Emily was on top of the World. Picking out furniture, going through wallpaper swatches, decorating the house, it was like she was having the time of her life. Her happiness was infectious.

Last month I was up in the attic doing some cleaning when I stumbled upon an old box. I opened it up to see what was inside. At first it was just some junk; old magazines, a tennis shoe, and a ratty football. I was just about to pick up the box and put it on the curb when I saw something else at the bottom. It was an old photo album. Skimming through it briefly, everyone in it seemed to be happy. I put it back without thinking much about it.

The next few weeks past quietly enough. We settled into a routine and got familiar with our neighbors. They were all pretty welcoming. They were polite and helpful but kept mostly to themselves. After coming home from work last week, I saw my next door neighbor Paul was taking out the garbage. After parking in my driveway, I gave him a brief wave and he took a few steps closer.

"Evening Ron," he greeted me with a nod. Paul reminded me of one of those character actors from back in the day. The kind who was always playing a tough old lawman in a Western. He has the demeanor nailed. The polite but don't mess with me son attitude. My dad is a lot like that, so I instantly felt comfortable with him. The secret is that deep down they are some of the most kindhearted people you would ever want to meet.

"How's it going Paul?"

"It's going fine. How are things with you?"

"Can't complain. How's it getting settled in."

"Ok."

"The Mrs. handling it ok? Moving is always hardest on the family." He was right on that. I suspect he was talking from personal experience, as he never saw his son anymore after he moved out to New Mexico.

"She's doing ok. She's tough."

"Seems that way. Good for her."

"Hey, I found an old photo album in the attic. What were the people who lived here before us like?" Houses were like your significant other's exes. You can't help but be a tad curious about who was there before you. Not to mention it could be important information at times.

"The Claytons?" he asked. "They was good people. Nice. The kind of people you'd see in a commercial for a minivan or something. Photogenic like you saw."

"Do you know why they moved?" He paused momentarily.

"No. They didn't really move per say. But I know why they left the house. The family disappeared."

"You're kidding,"

"Afraid not. One day years ago they went on vacation and never came back. Tragic."

"Does anyone know what happened?"

"No. Breaks your heart doesn't it? Happy family on vacation. Happens way more than people like to think."

"Sure does. Always good to see you Paul."

"You too Ron," I went inside with my mind still on what Paul told me. An entire family who walked these halls, ate in the same dining room, and slept under this roof just up and vanished. It's a weird feeling. Creepy too. What were their last memories here? Was it a happy one? What was the last meal they had here? The questions were impossible to answer, yet they kept bothering me.

Later that night I looked up the Claytons. They disappeared on the way home from a trip in Arizona in 2004. Since they were last seen near the desert, they suspected they got stranded or something and died of dehydration. My heart went out to them regardless of what happened. Not gonna lie, that fact stayed in the back of my mind. Happy families on vacation don't just disappear without a cause.

A few days ago I found out an elderly woman nearby died in her sleep. I never met her, but she lived in another development about 5 minutes away. Sounds tragic but not exactly surprising right? Well when they did the autopsy on Mrs. Hartfield they saw that she had died of anaphylaxis, caused by an allergic reaction she had to peanuts. Considering when they searched her house they found nothing peanut related anywhere, this didn't exactly sit well with people. Especially since when they interviewed her family they confirmed she didn't go out the day of her death and only ate foods she had at home.

When Paul told me this, I felt a shiver run up my spine. There was only one way that could have happened, and it went on right in my own backyard.

"The worst thing is they think it was someone she knew."

"Family member?" It was the only thing I could think of.

"Wish I could say it wasn't. But Mrs. Hartfield was too nice for her family. Like a doe amongst vultures." We stood there talking a bit longer, but since we didn't have much else to say we soon went inside. The next couple days were pretty uneasy for me, as I was keeping an eye on things. Not to mention I had a bit of a hard time sleeping.

Yesterday I was having my usual morning coffee while on my computer. Out of the corner of my eye I saw a breaking headline.

"Police make arrest in suspicious death of local woman." I clicked on it and it was about Mrs. Hartfield.

"After exhausting previous leads, police executed a search warrant late last night at a local residence. The owner of the house, contractor Daniel Layton 45, was seen earlier that day taking large amounts of jewelry to a pawn shop. The manager of the shop observed Mr. Layton behaving suspiciously and contacted authorities. The jewelry was subsequently identified as belonging to Mrs. Hartfield and removed from the home without anyone's knowledge or consent."

But it was the next section that made my skin crawl.

"Police also located a known associate of Mr. Layton, a Miss Carla Anderson. As Mrs. Hartfield's realtor, she was confirmed by her employers to have sold the house to the deceased. As a local realtor for almost 20 years, she has become known to homeowners all through the area. At the Layton residence, police found a key that was proved to work at the Hartfield residence. Upon being taken into custody, Mr. Layton confirms Anderson told him to pawn the jewelry and keep the profits. Both Ms. Anderson and Mr. Layton will be arraigned on charges tomorrow."

Right at the bottom was Carla's picture. It was the exact same one on the brochures she handed out at open houses.

But the worst to come happened today. After the did some digging, they found that Mrs. Hartfield wasn't the only person Carla sold a house to who died under suspicious circumstances. At least 5 other people in the area died under unusual circumstances. Every one of them bought a house from Carla. She was also helpful enough to sell the house to whoever moved in after it came up vacant again. The Clayton's were one of the first families in the area she sold a house to.

When I told Emily all this she was pretty upset, but I have to say she has calmed down a lot. We plan to move as soon as we can. I've also changed the locks and installed a deadbolt on all the doors for the rest of the time we're here.

PLEASE send help to Elkhorn, Montana by SpookyMarie

I'm not sure how long it's been since I've seen the sun. I remember reading about what would happen to our world if the sun simply ceased to exist. Plants and trees would stop producing oxygen and it would slowly get colder until we all eventually died out from either suffocation or hypothermia. We found out that leaving the town was a completely useless endeavor. No matter how many turns you took or how far you walked you would end up right back in town. A small group of hopeful individuals set off on foot with packs and provisions, promising to return with help. Haven't seen them since the first week the sun stopped coming up.

There was about twenty of us when it happened. I woke up early that day for my 4am opening shift at the grocery store. I preferred working at this time of hour as it was normally a peacefully dark walk that granted extra time to fully wake as the sun rose. I must've noticed it at around 7am, along with a few others. I normally take my first break when night crew leaves for the day so we can share a smoke outside with the cold air nipping at our faces and the birds chiming in on our conversations. This morning was no different, except there were no birds. It was extremely eerie, the silence.

When the store opens at 6am it normally brings in the early bird shoppers who are way too excited about being up early and the occasional night owl grabbing their alcoholic sleep aide. This morning was different. We didn't have a single customer by the time I went on my break. The oddest part about it all was that the sun was late rising. Jeanee was the first one to speak aloud what all of us were growing increasingly worried about.

"hey, what time is the sunrise today?" she said. I could sense she was uneasy about it but tried to pass it off as a nonchalant curiously more than her apparent anxiety would let on. I checked the local paper sitting on the rack beside us and sure enough, in big bold letters read "Sunrise- 5:56am" which was definitely concerning. Eventually our ten minute break ended and we all headed back inside, each of us glancing in the sky for a small hope we'd see any sign of that gray morning. It never came. The store flocked with almost everyone in town stocking up on water and grabbing everything off the shelves. Eventually the power went out so we had to close.

My town is fairly small, hidden in the mountains and trees with only dirt roads. we were the only grocery store in town, so people outside and around came here. I'm not sure why, but I live in a town where it's mostly retired miners so I think they just like the comfort of being around others. Better than being left alone with your own thoughts I guess, especially in a time of crisis. We decided to hunker down at the store, locking the doors and letting people in as they showed up. It was about 2pm at this point and the sun had still not shown its face. It was strange, seeing my small town shrouded in darkness long after we should've been bathed in warm sunlight.

My boss was made for this sort of thing. He was kind of a dick and had the attitude of a drill sergeant but in the midst of disaster he immediately took charge like he'd been waiting his whole life for that moment to shine and I believe that's one of the few reasons we've survived this long. He's dead now, happened last week while out with a group scavenging for burnable wood. They said it was a mountain lion, their bloody spots on their clothes made me sceptical, but I was too much of a pussy to say anything.

The first few days was when we noticed our communications were down. We also noticed it was getting colder. Not by a lot at first, but enough to notice. Myself and a few of my coworkers were involuntarily volunteered to head to the next town over and see if they were able to offer assistance. Like I said before, I worked in a community of mostly retired older men so it was a lot harder for some of the others than it would be for 4 younger guys to complete the task.

We loaded up our packs with a few things for the road, water bottles and a few snacks, and headed out. I think Mark was the first one to notice we were going in circles. We had been walking for well over a few hours and should've reached the next town over by now. It was as if we would be reset somehow and we'd just be right back in town. Eventually I made a few other turns and our suspicion was correct when we ended up right back in front of the grocery store. My town is densely forested so we weren't able to really track if we had somehow gone in a complete circle, but I've walked this road to and from work for years, it shouldn't have fucking changed. I know for a fact I was headed in the right direction and going straight, so to end up right back where we started pissed me off more than frightened me.

All that trip did was waste energy, provisions, and time. It didn't help that all of us were extremely groggy, our bodies unable to sync up with the sunrise/sunset. After another two hour trip our suspicions were proven, and with long, defeated steps we made our way to the front stoop of the store. All of us taking a seat in the cold, dark silence. None of it made sense. We would leave only to find ourselves right back where we started with no memory of how we got back to that spot. I think we were growing delirious from the lack of sunlight.

When we told the others, the first reaction we were greeted with was irrevocable denial. We took a wrong turn, didn't pay attention, should've brought a map, etc. But after another group was sent out with the same results, panic ensued. There was an immediate outcry for help we all knew would not arrive. People grabbed what they could, and took off through the doors and out into the darkness,presumably to their homes, where they would shut themselves in left alone with no company other than their own hopeful beliefs of help arriving.

There was about twenty of us, but that was a few weeks ago. Myself and two others were able to hide out in one of the nearby homes across the road from the store and make food runs when needed. I wish I could say we stayed in the store, considering there was still food left, but it had gotten so cold, and with the roof caving in from the onslaught of snow it just couldn't keep anyone warm. Its been below 20 these last few nights and it makes me sick to my stomach knowing that there are probably only a few of us left that are young enough to survive this insane weather. It's been getting harder to breathe and the trees are starting to die. It started snowing again last night.

I don't know how much longer we'll have. I'm not even sure if this will reach anyone, but if it does, my name is Hogan Graeseth, please send help to Elkhorn, Montana. We are dying. We can't leave town, and the power has long gone out. The sun is gone. It's getting colder with the snow and I don't think we'll last another night.

Something weird is happening in my Airbnb. by eraab953

I'm out of town for a friend’s wedding. My friend Kirk, his girlfriend Linnea, and our friend John all split an Airbnb together - a beautiful, secluded house in the middle of nowhere. Once we were done making our way up the treacherous hill, it felt nice to get out of our comfort zone and away from the city noise. Well, until the weird shit started happening.

The wedding was yesterday. Beautiful ceremony, great food, and lots of dancing. We spent the next morning and afternoon too hungover to do anything and by the time night rolled around it started storming so we stayed in. Good thing we stocked up on plenty of booze. We ordered some pizza and we were set.

We were drinking, talked about the wedding, Kirk dodged some questions from Linnea passively asking about when they were going to finally tie the knot. Then Linnea asked, "Hey, did anyone hear anything strange last night?"

I was so deep in my drunken slumber an earthquake wouldn't have woken me up.

"No, what did you hear? One of the animals out there?”

"I don't know, but it sounded like someone humming?" Whatever it was, seems like the rest of us all slept through it.

After polishing off the second bottle of wine, Kirk asked, "Why don't we play a game?"

I remembered seeing some board games in the basement while we were snooping around the place earlier. We went down there and found the usual suspects in the closet: Monopoly, Scrabble, Yahtzee.

"Oh, I think I found what we're looking for!" Linnea was holding a navy blue box.

"Is that Pictionary?" asked Kirk. This one had to be popular with guests - there was barely any dust on it.

We opened it up and got ready to play, me and John against Kirk and Linnea, naturally. The first card was "Guitar". She beat me that round - damn could she draw fast.

By the fifth round we started getting into the game, yelling encouragements and well-meaning insults at each other. But at the beginning of this round, Linnea flipped a page from her drawing pad and paused. She looked like someone slammed the brakes in her head.

"What's wrong? Linnea, it's your turn to draw." Kirk looked annoyed. "Don't tell me you want to stop now. This was your idea."

Her eyes were still fixed on the drawing pad. "Look at this." She handed it over.

"So?" I asked. "The owners played a few rounds. Or some other guests played." She pointed at the page. I took a closer look. It was a pentagram with numbers accompanying each angle.

"What was the card they picked?" John asked, turning to Linnea. "Your anniversary?"

"Shut up dude." She started flipping through the book. There were more sketches. A lot more. One was a goat head with weird markings around it. Someone had to have went over the timer for that one. A few other pages had images I did not recognize. One page was just words. Not sure what language they were in, but definitely not English. And the ink looked weird...whoever it was wasn’t using the same worn-out pens from the box.

"Did anyone hear that?" Kirk made a hushing gesture with his hands.

"Hear what?" I asked. He put a finger to his lips. And then I heard it. Footsteps. They were faint, but there. Someone was trying to not be heard.

"There's someone up there!" said Linnea, a little too loud. "Do we call the police?"

"Do you get service out here?" I replied. We checked our phones - none of us had a bar showing. This was a problem throughout the property.

"Maybe it's one of their kids?" proposed John. We never met the owners, we just exchanged some texts letting us know where the keys were, how to use the coffee maker, and some food recommendations. I got the vibe they were an older married couple, them having kids wasn't out of the question. But one of them stopping by unannounced sure as shit was.

"I guess it's possible?"

John stood. “I’m going up.”

Linnea rushed to her feet. “Dude, are you nuts?” . "Just a little," he gave a wink. He's always had a thing for her. Then again, John had a thing for everyone. He started up the stairs, which turned to the right halfway, one hand holding the bannister, the other gripping the neck of an empty beer bottle.

"Why are we splitting off?" I've seen a few horror flicks in my day. That shit wasn’t happening to me. We followed him up. Nothing seemed out of place. Then again, how would we know? We were just guests here. This 4.5-star, "Chill Farmhouse Getaway".

Light flashed through the window, the power going out before the thunder could meet up with it.

This was going great. We all booted up the Flashlight app. "Breaker's in the garage probably?" I didn't see it in the basement.

"Your guess is as good as mine," Linnea was going through the kitchen drawers, phone in hand. "There's gotta be some candles around here somewh - FUCK!" Bright white light filled the room, and then we saw it.

A tall, thin hooded figure was facing the window, looking into the kitchen. Looking at us. After the light retreated so did our view of him (or her, it was too dark to see outside).

"Did you guys see that?" There was a slight whimper in her voice. We shined our phones out the window. Whatever it was, it was gone. I didn't want to stay another second.

"We're getting out of here."

Kirk and Linnea both nodded. John was the only one in disagreement. "For real guys?"

Big fucking "yep."

"And what about all our stuff? If someone's robbing us he's probably just waiting for us to leave."

"Let him. We're going, with or without you." The three of us headed to the door, John gave one last eyeroll and followed us. I turned the door handle. Did any of us even remember to lock this thing?

I slowly opened the door into the rain, poked my head out and looked around. It was dark, I couldn’t see anything. The car was in the driveway which through the front patio past the fence. We hurried towards it, frantically pulling at the handles when we got to the car. I forgot to unlock the door.

"Hurry!" Linnea berated me as I rummaged through my jacket looking for the keys.

"I'm trying!" I found the keys and we all got in. I jammed it into the ignition and gave a twist. Nothing. I tried again and again. The car was dead.

"Last time we rent a Kia. I guess we'll just go back in?" John opened the passenger side door. I guess we had to follow him back. We walked back through the fence and stopped in our tracks. The door to the house was open.

I looked at Kirk, the last one out the door. "Did you leave it open?"

"I don't know man. The wind could've blown it open!"

"Well, I'm going in," John got out of the car. "No way in hell I'm walking down that curvy ass road in this rain. I'll take my chances with whatever we all think we might of saw out there." We followed him back into the house, it was dark and still.

"Let's check out that breaker," John said tapping Kirk on the shoulder. After they went to the garage, I sat with Linnea, listening and looking for signs of an intruder. That's when we saw a faint light coming from outside.

"A car's pulling up!" Linnea looked out the kitchen window. We couldn't see through the fence but we saw the light continue to grow for a minute or two and then creeped away. Did they leave and come back?

"Someone's coming!" She was whispering loudly now, crouched by the door. She motioned me to get on the other side. She was right. Even through the rain I could hear footsteps walking up the concrete patio. There was a loud knock. Linnea gave me a look. What did she want me to do? And then the door opened.

I acted fast. I grabbed the intruder by the neck and brought him down onto the kitchen tile. He yelled in surprise and tried to get back on his feet.

"GOT YOU NOW YOU BASTARD!" Linnea was holding a baseball bat in both hands over her head. Where did she find that?

"Linnea! No!" It was John.

"Huh?"

"It's Derek!" Derek? I got a look at his face and a mixture of relief and guilt came over me. Derek was a friend of the groom who shared our wedding table. Him and John really hit it off.

"What are you doing here?"

"I invited him," said John as he helped him to his feet.

"Yeah, John texted me and said you guys were partying so I got in an Uber." He dusted himself off. "He didn't tell me you were into this MMA shit though."

"Sorry about that." I turned back to John. "Why didn't you tell us?"

"Oh, I don't know, I guess it slipped my mind while everyone's been freaking out about this supposed axe murderer in the woods."

"The what?" Derek looked confused. "Clearly I came at a bad time."

"Where's Kirk?" asked Linnea.

"He went back to the basement to grab his knife he left down there."

"And you didn't go with him? What's wrong with you?!"

"Well, I was about to and then I heard the commotion up here and decided I was needed elsewhere."

We headed over to the basement stairs. I yelled down, but didn't hear anything back. We all gave an unsure look to each other and started slowly walking down. I flashed the light from my phone, the battery just at 25% now, from one end of the room to the other. No sign of anyone.

"Why did he go down there by himself?" Linnea was almost crying now. The idiot was probably feeling a bit emasculated in front of John, who was now putting an arm around her to comfort her.

We all started calling his name from different parts of the house. Nothing.

That's when the power came back. The lights flashed on followed by a beep from the microwave.

Finally, something was going our way. "Well, what do we do?" I asked before feeling a slight vibration in my pocket.

I pulled out my phone, and so did everyone else, except for Derek. Now that the power was back so was the WiFi, and someone messaged our group chat. I looked at the icon in the bottom right of my screen. It was Kirk. I gave it a tap.

Stay with us

We all just looked at each other.

"Uhhh," Derek broke the silence. "Someone want to fill me in here?"

"I think he's messing with us," said John, ignoring Derek. Linnea gave him a hard slap and sat on the couch with her head in her hands.

We don't know what to do. We're sitting in the living room now so I'm doing what I always do when I'm unsure of something, I just start writing to collect my thoughts. I'll continue when I have an update.

The Ashland House by lunalikesleopards

Hi. My name is Luna (not my birth name, but I really hate the Mary Sue, First Lady, "Can I speak to your manager" one I was born with, so please don't ask.) I'm an empath. Some people describe being an empath as a paranormal thing, but I don't view it that way. I just see it as being really sensitive. Basically, I feel other people's emotions like they're mine. It might sound cool to someone who hasn't experienced it, but it's actually a bummer, if I'm being honest. A lot of people in the world are really sad and angry, and more than you'd think. It sucks having to feel people's pain all the time. I had to drop out of CNA training because almost every patient's feelings made me want to cry, and many did make me cry. It's impossible to be professional when you feel that way all the time. I think it'll become pretty clear why this is relevant to my story.

This story really happened to me when I was fourteen. I know most people aren't going to believe it, and that's okay. I just want to write it down for people to enjoy, whether they laugh at it, are scared by it, or maybe even relate to it. If you relate to it, please let me know. I'd love to talk to someone who's had a similar experience. So without further ado, here's my telling of what happened, combined with some parts that my mother told me later because I wasn't there.

When I was fourteen, my mom and I had a cozy rental house in Ashland, Oregon. It was built in 1944, but it kept well. You can go see it if you want, and by "go see it" I mean you can look at Google Maps. 374 Avery Street. It had a small fenced grassy yard, front and back, which was convenient for our Labrador and Australian Shepherd mix, Annie. I had a pretty close friend who lived across the street and down two houses. We shared a passion for talking about the paranormal. While she wasn't necessarily an empath, she had another special ability. Ghosts showed themselves to her all the time. Always benevolent ones, lucky enough for her. She'd tell me the stories of when she was a little girl, camping with her parents. The woods made her see a lot more ghosts. One of my favorites she'd tell was the one where she was sitting crossed-legged, chin in her hands, swaying back and forth gently. Her mom came up and asked her why she was doing that.

"The people, Mommy, they're dancing. They're dancing!" she yelled happily. Her mother never saw anyone, but apparently what my friend saw were dozens of ballroom dancers.

I'll just call my friend A because I haven't talked to her in years and don't know how to get a hold of her, so I can't ask her if she's okay with being in the story. I'll call her mother L, because she's in this story too.

The house we lived in looked almost like a perfect square, but the inside architecture was a little more complicated. It felt sort of cramped and angular. My room felt very separate from the rest of the house, because it used to be the garage. You had to go out a door, down some steps and across the laundry room into a short, skinny hallway to get into it. It had nice carpet inside, and we had painted the walls black and the ceiling dark purple (I had a pretty intense Goth streak in high school). The room didn't have much furniture, but I liked it that way. Just a comfy mattress and a desk where I could do homework and draw all the angsty shit that Goth teenagers draw. Across from my room and to the left, in the laundry room, was the door to the backyard. On the right, up the steps, was the door to the house.

Everything started one night when I was going to bed. I had never been afraid of the dark at this time, so I switched off the lights and climbed into bed without having to think about it. With my walls painted black and my curtains pulled shut over the only window, this made my room almost pitch black. As I put one foot in the bed and started to slide it under the covers, a light caught my eye, almost violently. Like I said, I wasn't afraid of the dark, but that didn't mean I was brave. I jumped backwards onto my mattress and crouched against the wall where a headboard would have been if the bed had one. I blinked intensely, trying to focus my eyes on the light in my room. My eyes focused too slowly, like there was water in them, and the light seemed to sway gently back and forth. Finally my eyes focused on the light and I recognized it as a figure. It was sitting in my chair. It was sitting at my fucking desk.

The figure didn't have a face or even seem to have arms, it was just a very vaguely human-shaped beam of light, but even so... I could feel it looking at me. And I knew it didn't like me. I didn't know why, but I felt an intense anger that I've never felt before in my life. Like it wanted me to die.

I don't know how I broke myself out of the paralysis of the fear, but I somehow managed to scramble out of bed and make a mad dash for my mom's room. While I ran, I screamed as loud as I could, trying to alert my mom and maybe, if I was lucky, scare away whatever was in my room. I pulled open the door to the laundry room, beating my bare feet on the cold concrete as I raced for the door into the house. I felt my pulse beating in my neck like I had never felt it before. When I got up the steps, I clumsily groped and yanked on the doorknob with hands made rubber by fear. I was sure it was locked for a moment, but it turns out I was just so scared that I wasn't opening it properly, and it was an old door, so you really had to pull. I almost fell backwards down the steps and into the laundry room with the force of pulling the door open, but thankfully my legs carried me onto the wood floor of the house and I slammed the door shut behind me, forcing all of my weight behind it as if it could be "extra closed." I closed the deadbolt too, while simultaneously telling myself that that was stupid because whatever that was could probably go right through doors. I jogged down the short hallway into my mom's room and flung myself across her bed.

"Mom! Mom!" I yelled. She groaned and rolled over and looked at me. It was about 2am and my Mom does not like being woken up, and she definitely doesn't believe in things that go bump in the night (or at least she didn't used to.) But she listened to my recounting of what had happened sleepily, suggested I had been having a bad dream, said I could sleep with her if I needed to, and went back to sleep. I didn't need her to believe me. I was just relieved that I didn't have to go back in that room that night. I lay in her bed with the covers up to my nose for hours before finally falling asleep.

The next day was Monday. I woke up in my mom's room and realized I would have to go back into my room to get clothes for school. I was obviously not thrilled at the idea. I was particularly not thrilled because my Mom had already left to do errands or something, so I was alone in the house. I opened all the curtains in the main part of the house, because sunlight has always made me feel safer. Then I slowly opened the door to the laundry room, and walked down the steps. Then I heard barking from the backyard. It was Annie. I opened the back door, looked down at her in front of me, and realized she was facing the house. I looked at her and talked to her the way I've talked to animals since I was little, like they could understand me, "Annie, were you... barking at the house?" She looked at me, and then back towards where she had been looking before. I didn't even have to look behind me to know that she had been barking straight at my room.

At this point I was creeped out enough to step out of the house and into the yard with her. For some reason it didn't feel right to close the door behind me, so I didn't. I stroked the dog's head and told her everything would be alright. I think she could tell I didn't believe that, because she barked at my room again in response. I grabbed her leash from the hook outside the door, clipped it on, and decided to get us the Hell out of there. That feeling of being watched from the other night was still eating away at the back of my head, even as I crossed the street to A's house.

I found her on her porch, lazily eating dried figs.

"What's the matter with you? You look like you seen a ghost, bruthaaaa," she said. For all I knew, she could have been quoting a movie or a song or just being her normal dorky self but I didn't care at the time or bother to ask.

"I did see a ghost, A. In my house. In my room." She perked up at this, because to her ghosts meant fun and entertainment, maybe even friendship.

"Fuck yaaaaa! Tell me about your new buddy," she said. I didn't even know how to proceed at this point. I couldn't humor her, but I was also going to feel bad for unsettling her kind of sweet bond with the supernatural. Oh well. I just had to do it.

"This one isn't a buddy, A. I think it might be a demon or something. It's really fucking creepy." I tried to explain what had happened and what I had felt. She leaned back a bit and her brow furrowed.

"Okay, well I should go meet this thing," she said with a seriousness I didn't usually see in her, "but I should probably tell you some stuff about ghosts I haven't told you yet, first." I sat myself and Annie down on the porch to listen. She told me a few things about what she called ghost manners.

"The most important rule," she said "is to always give them their space. If you get too close to them, they might freak out or something. They're like, unstable." I agreed that I would give the entity its space.

We walked back to my house together, slowly as if we both expected something to happen on our way there. I didn't feel watched anymore. Maybe it was because I was with A. When we got to the back door, I realized I had left it open all this time. What I quickly realized afterwards was that we wouldn't have to go into my room to meet the figure of light. Because it was standing in the hallway to my bedroom. I was instantly paralyzed. Annie growled a deep, warning growl and then began barking. A seemed unphased, however.

"I don't know why you were afraid of this one, it seems sweet," she said. That was when, to my horror, my friend began walking towards the figure with her arms outstretched like she wanted to hug it.

I wanted to yell "Please don't" or something, anything, but my mouth remained frozen with the rest of my body. I had to watch, excruciatingly and with increasing panic as A stepped closer and closer to the figure, crossing the threshold into the laundry room. I didn't know what it was capable of, but all I could think of was the anger it had placed in me. If it wanted me to die, what would it do to people who cared about me? That was when my mom finally came home. Thankfully she came in the back way.

"Hey, did I hear A? What are you guys up to? Why is Annie barking?" She didn't sound worried, but her face looked worried as soon as she saw me, standing frozen in place with our snarling dog, who was usually not aggressive at all. "What's going on?" she asked. I could move now but still couldn't answer her. My eyes darted back to A who had lowered her arms, and was now standing slumped over like a wet noodle. The figure was gone. My mom peeked in the house and saw my friend standing there strangely, walked up to her and shook her shoulder. A gasped and turned around to face my mom. Her bottom lip started to quiver.

"What did I do?" she asked.

"What do you mean, A? You were just standing here. Are you okay?" My mom asked.

A shook her head and looked like she was trying really hard not to cry. My mom looked back at me, confused, "What the Hell is going on with you guys?" "I'm sorry, Ms. S. We were just kiddin'. We're fine," she said. She walked out into the yard next to me and shook my arm. "Uh yeah, we're okay," I agreed.

"If that was supposed to be a prank, it wasn't a very funny one," she said, concerned. She looked me up and down and realized she had come home to an unshowered teenager who had not gone to school. She wasn't happy about it, but she knew her divorce from my Dad had been hard on me, and I think she wanted to cut me some slack. She just told me to go to school tomorrow. Then she asked us to come inside. A and I complied. Annie did not.

Annie had always been extremely obedient and eager-to-please for my Mom. She never said no to her. It would break her canine heart. So for her to stand in defiance of my mother was unusual, to say the least. We tried treats, firm voices and everything in between. We even tried to carry her into the house, but she whimpered so pitifully that we finally left her alone. My mom went into the kitchen and started putting away the groceries she'd bought. A and I sat on the living room couch together, heads stuck together, thick as thieves.

"So what really happened to you?" I asked her.

"I didn't want to touch it, girl. It was, like... calling me. It made it seem like it was just the best damn idea I ever had to go right to it. But I knew it was wrong at the same time. I don't know. That's not like any ghost I ever met before." I agreed. Definitely not a benevolent ballroom dancer.

Annie stayed out in the yard this whole time. Occasionally she would let out another bark, and I was pretty sure I knew in exactly which direction.

When it got dark and A had gone home, I asked my Mom if I could sleep in her room again. She sort of looked at me as if to say, "You know you're fourteen, right?" but if that was what she was thinking, she didn't say so. Instead she suggested that A come back over and have a sleepover, probably thinking that that would make my room feel fun again, and less scary. It wasn't a bad idea from her perspective, but I was way too freaked out to agree. I said I'd rather just not go in that room tonight. So she agreed, "For now."

The next morning, my Mom went to talk to A's mother L, who was sort of a faith healer or a medicine woman or something. Between Annie sleeping outside the night before (which she had never done), and me being terrified of my own room, my mom had decided that it was time to try taking this seriously. She had a chat with L about what had been going on (the part she knew anyway), and L seemed to know what to do immediately. She gathered some things into a medium-sized velvet bag and headed over to our house that moment.

My mom and L went into my bedroom, while me and A watched curiously from the door. We were both the type who pretended to be brave but really weren't. We were pretty okay with letting our moms handle whatever demon-ghost-light-thing had decided to take up residence in my room. L lit some sage, and walked around the room wafting it into each corner. She spoke to my mom and us (and what she called the "Spirit") while she did this.

"We've just got to let the Spirit know that it's not welcome here anymore. We acknowledge you and we appreciate you, Spirit, but it's time for you to go now." she said.

It was all very gentle and sweet. Exactly what you'd expect from a carefree hippie mom who called herself a healer. The whole process took about half an hour. We thanked L afterwards, and she and A went home.

It wasn't very long before I realized that the cleansing hadn't worked. Only about an hour later, I was sitting in my desk chair, doodling a manga character I liked at the time, when I felt like I was being stared at again. No, KNEW I was being stared at again. There was no doubt. Then the anger started to seep back in. The anger at me. The kind of anger you have at someone who's done you wrong a thousand times. I tried not to look at anything, I was terrified of seeing the figure again. I put my arm over my face and made my way carefully but hurriedly into the laundry room. I knew it would be easier to get into the backyard than the house, so I ran out into the backyard and grabbed Annie. I buried my face in her fur and cried out of fear and frustration. The thing was supposed to be gone. I felt failed by L, and just kind of failed by life. "I shouldn't have to be afraid of my own room," I said out loud into Annie's warm comforting shoulder. She normally would have licked me to comfort me, but she was too focused on doing what she'd done for two days now: staring at my room, and occasionally barking at it.

My mom came home once again to a teen wearing the same clothes she'd slept in and desperately clinging to the dog.

"Alright, that's it," she said. She wasn't mad at me, she was mad at whatever was in my room. And she didn't even believe in whatever was in my room. She told me to come inside and we went into the kitchen. She handed me the phone and told me to call A and have her come over.

"Why?" I asked.

"I don't want you to be alone," she said, "but me and whatever that thing is need to have a TALK." She said the last word through her teeth, gritted with determination.

When A came over, we huddled together on the couch, a bit shaken by the situation, but also fascinated by whatever was going to take place. My mom started to go into the laundry room alone, and I stopped her. "I should go with you," I said. "This thing wants me. It might not even show up if it's just you." My mom still didn't believe in any of this, but she had always trusted me in the past when I seemed sure about what I was doing. So we both went in together, while A waited in the living room. I sat down on my bed, trying to recreate the situation that had first made it appear. My mom stood in the middle of the room, waiting for me to tell her if I saw or felt anything. It didn't take long. I didn't see it externally this time, but in my head. It was like it was forcing its likeness into my mind. I saw the angriest, most hateful face I've ever even imagined. It was twisted, bitter, and definitely male.

I don't know if you believe in energy, but I do. Whenever I've met a trans person, for instance, I immediately see them as the gender they know they were born as, even if they're presenting themselves as cis. I'm telling you this because I want you to know why I say that this face was definitely male. It didn't have any actual features that would tell you anything about its age, gender, race, or anything like that. It was more like the embodiment of what the expressions of anger and hatred look like. The energy I felt though, was that of an older man.

If he was angry before, now he was raging. He filled my head with not only his own hatred, but SELF-hatred. I felt like I didn't deserve to live. I felt like he deserved to kill me. I was still scared, but in that moment, I almost accepted these things as fact. My Mom asked something like if the "Spirit" was calming down, or being nicer. "No! No!" I screamed. "He's worse! It's so much worse!" I was crying at this point, and my Mom had had enough of my torment. She sent me out to the living room to be with my friend. I let A hug me but tried really hard to stop crying. I didn't want to look like a total wimp in front of my friend. I already felt horribly guilty for leaving my mom in that room alone. I heard the door close.

This is one of those times when I wasn't there, so this next part is just what my mom told me:

Mom closed the door behind her, and shut off the lights. You might be thinking "Why on Earth...?" but that's just because you don't know my mom. She's a fighter. She never runs from confrontation, she owns it. And if you mess with her kid, that's when you really get to see her teeth. She wanted this thing to know without a doubt that she was not afraid of it and that she was going to win. She was a little frightened, but there was no way she was going to let this thing know it. She stepped into the middle of the room again and called out to it, or... him: "I know you're here. I know you're angry. You may even be justified in your anger. But it's not my family that hurt you. This is my family, and now this is my home. You have to leave."

That is when my mom finally got to meet him. I'm not sure exactly what she saw or felt, but when I described the figure and the feelings of anger and hatred to her, she said "Yep. That's who I met." I do know that she felt the same rage and the bitterness from him that I had felt, and that she literally pushed through it. That's right. She opened the window, and pushed this non-physical thing out of the window with her physical hands. This still doesn't make sense to me, but you'll see why I believe that she did it in a moment.

Mom came back into the house and looked at us with a look of triumph. Not only had she (probably) rid my room of its unwanted inhabitant, but guess who was trailing at her feet? Annie had come back inside for the first time in days. She didn't exactly look calm, but the glazed-over stare was at least gone. You could tell my mom felt really good about protecting her family and her home. We wanted to applaud her, but we were still so skeptical that the thing was gone. We just sort of went "Yaaaaay," desperately hoping that she was right and that the Spirit or whatever it was had gone out the window.

That was when all three of us jumped at the same time. Because my room used to be the garage, the driveway and therefore our car, was right outside my bedroom window. We had jumped because the car had begun both shrieking and flashing. The shrieking was some kind of high-pitched alarm that we weren't even aware the car had. The flashing came from various small red lights, also new to us. The car literally looked insane. The sound was horrendous. We all went to the window and stared at the car for a few moments, before my Mom went out and decided to do something about it.

I'm not sure exactly what she did, but I think she just knocked around in the car until the alarm stopped. She looked a little shaken when she came back in, but fine, thankfully. She then took the sage L had left and cleansed the car with it. She invited the Spirit to go up and out the little sunroof. Maybe that was a more preferable direction to go than the sideways trip through my window. She felt a little silly out in our driveway, burning sage in the car, and doing what probably looked like talking to herself. Especially when the local college's night classes let out and adult students began to walk by. She kept at it though, and it must have worked, because that was finally the last we heard from our Spirit.

About a week later, my mom was installing a new fence in the front yard so that Annie could go all the way around the house, instead of just in the backyard. While she was working, a man came up to her and introduced himself as the owner of the duplex behind our house. They chatted for a while about this and that, before he asked her, "So, you know what happened in that house?" My Mom told him she didn't, and he began to explain.

Apparently an old man had lived in our house before us, a man who no one ever came to visit. The way he left this world is not pretty, so if you're squeamish, you might not want to read this last part. I don't know if the man ever had a helper or a caretaker, but if he did, they stopped coming. The man lay in his bed for days, defecating on himself, just waiting for someone to find him. Eventually he died that way, alone in his bed covered in mess and probably unspeakably lonely. When my mom heard this, I'm sure her eyes must have widened. She probably passed it off as some other expression, but I know she had to have been thinking about what we experienced in our house. I'm not saying this is the case, but it would make sense to me if the man had died alone because he had led a cruel and selfish life. I feel almost guilty inferring this, as if he can hear me. It's just that I don't think his sad death alone would have caused the type of anger that me and my Mom both felt.

Anyway... I hope he found a better place through that sunroof.

The house I grew up in by FUZZ_buster

This is the tale of experiences I had growing up in an old house in rural New York. I figured this was an appropriate place to post it.

Growing up, my house always seemed a little off. I never really felt comfortable there. It could have been because of my dysfunctional family. It could have been because we never really have felt comfortable with each other. I don't know.

But I can tell you that i am convinced that place is haunted as shit. Even now that my parents are dead and gone I hate going there. It's on the market for what my family owes in taxes. If anyone wants a cheap property they are welcome to it. No joke. PM me. The house was built around 1870. It's a plank house; nothing special. And it needs a lot of work (obviously a good spritual cleansing, too).

When I was young, I shared a room with my two sisters. My brother had his own room down the hall. Our room was always the coldest in the house. It used to be the attic, but my father built an addition on the house when I was born to accommodate his three daughters, so it was the biggest bedroom in the house.

My first memory of it being not quite right was when I was about 6. I have posted about this before, but it still is relevant to this story. My mother sent me to bed early one night and I remember standing in my room and seeing one of my sister's shoes being drawn slowly under the dust ruffle of her bed. I screamed my head off and my mother didn't believe me. I saw it, though. I can still see it vividly.

A few weeks later I was also the first to go to bed. I was facing the back window getting PJ's out of my dresser when I felt breath on the back of my neck and heard someone whisper my name in my ear. I freaked the hell out, and my father was already in bed at the other end of the hall, so I ran to him. He didn't believe me either, although he followed me back to my room with a baseball bat. I tearfully insisted that it happened, and although I could most often count on him to listen to me, he still just laughed and kissed my head and put me to bed. I remember not sleeping much that night. There was a heaviness; a presence I couldn't justify or explain. That feeling remains. I still feel it when I'm there.

Nothing much happened for a few years after that except the occasional missing item that would eventually turn up exactly where you would expect it, or an unexplainable cold spot here and there. But we're on the Canada border, so cold spots are a given. All could be kind-of explained.

One night, however, I was in my brother's room doing homework. I was about 16 and he had moved out, so I had turned his room into my office. It was late for an overachieving high school student, maybe 10 p.m. or so, and I saw a little girl out of the corner of my eye. She looked just like my 3-year-old niece who lived in one of my parents' properties with my sister a few doors down. I turned to ask her what she was doing there so late. There was nothing there, but the room had gotten really cold, and it was late May. I figured maybe I was just tired and went to bed, knowing in the back of my mind what I saw was not a figment of my imagination. But I was almost a grownup, right? I couldn't be seeing shit like that, right?

A few days later, my dad told my family he also saw a little girl in the hallway outside his room. Everybody but me laughed at him.

There are other things that happened (like my hair getting pulled by unseen hands, feeling like I was being touched A LOT, etc.), but to make a long story short, we found out a short while later that a little girl had fallen out of one of the upstairs windows and died not long after the house was built. That still sends chills down my spine.

I have more experiences if anyone would like to hear them, but thought I would share this tidbit with you all. Please excuse my formatting and any typos. I'm on mobile.

Now get some sleep, you insomniacs.

The House of Demons by CynicHappy

Before all this happened, in the fall of 2016, I was a journalist best-known for my articles on the paranormal-or, rather, bullshit disguised as the paranormal. My career revolved around disproving various mysteries and conspiracy theories, exposing lies and attempting to turn people into skeptics. And, for the most part, the stories I investigated did turn out to be fake. I never imagined I'd encounter anything genuine. That is, until the House of Demons.

Now, I know what you're thinking: this is just another story about an asshole skeptic who gets their comeuppance and becomes a believer. That isn't exactly untrue. But there is far more to this story than me learning my lesson the hard way.

I had been contacted by a young woman whose father had recently been admitted to a mental hospital. The police had been called to his house after neighbours reported hearing screams, and found the poor man stumbling around his living room, covered in blood and screaming about things living in the walls. He had gnawed chunks of flesh from his arms and broken most of the furniture. The doctors believed he was suffering from psychosis, but his daughter, Keira, was convinced it was something else entirely.

"Something in that house terrified him," she told me over the phone. "Whatever he saw in there... it drove him insane."

Keira went on to explain the history of the house she had grown up in. Built in the late 1940s, it was rumoured that the original owners had been devil-worshippers. They had died in a mysterious accident, and since then, an endless string of paranormal events had been reported by anyone who lived there.

Most of the stories Keira told me were pretty freaky, but, in my jaded opinion, too over the top to be believable. Like the old lady with glowing red eyes who chased people away from the property, screaming and waving a bloody knife. Or the man found dead in the bathtub, his throat slit and the words HE'S COMING painted on the wall with his blood. Or the entire family that vanished into thin air, leaving nothing but patches of burnt rug in their living room. Keira had spoken to previous owners, and documented anything she found noteworthy.

"Tell me about your own experiences in the house," I urged.

Keira explained that her own family had moved into the house when Keira was seven years old, and that their life there had been fairly mellow-at least in comparison to some of the other stories. This, Keira believed, was because her parents were devout Catholics who prayed every day and had religious symbols on display in every room. Still, there were many unexplained sightings and noises, and an inexplicable dread that crept in on the darkest nights, a dread that nobody could shake off.

After Keira's mother passed away, her father went a little crazy and began reporting strange events with alarming frequency. While Keira worried for his mental state, she had no doubt he was telling the truth. In the weeks leading up to his sudden breakdown, he had been complaining about something "watching him at night" and whispering horrible things in his ear.

"I've read your work," said Keira. "I know you like to disprove paranormal claims. But this story is true. The people in my town... they call it the House of Demons."

I sighed, pinching the bridge of my nose. "Ma'am, I'm very sorry about your father's condition, but I don't think-"

"Please, Mrs. Johnston. Everyone thinks my dad is insane; I want people to know what really happened in there."

"How do you know he'll even talk to me?"

"He will. Believe me."

And so, a week later, I kissed my husband and four-year-old daughter goodbye, before boarding an airplane that would take me from my home in Vancouver to Ontario. After landing in the city, I picked up a rental car and drove out to the small town where the dreaded House of Demons stood.

Keira met me at a local coffee shop. She was a petite blonde with mascara-heavy blue eyes, dressed in a black sleeveless turtleneck and faded jeans. She stood up as soon as I walked in. "Amelia Johnston?"

"Yes." I extended my hand, and she shook it. "It's nice to meet you."

She smiled. "Thank you for coming."

Over coffee, she gave me an update on her father, a sixty-three-year-old man named Edwin Montgomery. "They've put him on anti-psychotic drugs, but he's still pretty messed up. Still, he's agreed to talk to you."

I still didn't believe I was really dealing with a haunted house case, but nonetheless, I felt bad for Keira. She was obviously shaken about her father and what he might have gone through. Given his state, I wasn't so sure interviewing him would be a good idea, but I couldn't turn back now.

After finishing our coffees and paying the bill, Keira and I drove out to the facility where Edwin was being held. A nurse escorted us to his room, and what I saw left me nearly speechless.

Edwin Montgomery was strapped to his bed, his arms heavily bandaged. His dishevelled white hair had the texture of dry straw, and his blue eyes, sunken deep within the bony hollows of his sockets, held the glazed, haunted look of a soldier returning from war. A man who had literally seen Hell.

"Daddy?" Keira spoke very quietly, as if any sudden noise would send her father off the deep end. "This is Amelia Johnston. That journalist I was telling you about. She wants to talk to you."

Very slowly, Edwin turned his head and looked right at me. Or rather, past me, at the faded green wall. His chapped, bluish lips moved, forming words without a voice.

I sat in the chair next to his bed and stared at him for a moment, unsure of how to proceed. Edwin just kept staring at me. Keira stood off to the side, biting her lip. Finally, I broke the silence myself.

"Edwin. Can you tell me what happened? About why you were sent here?"

He blinked, and I knew I had gotten through to him.

"It's... it's nice to meet you," he rasped.

"You too."

"They probably told you I'm crazy. But it isn't true."

"I don't think you're crazy," I lied, uncapping my pen. "But I am curious about what happened."

Edwin sighed, closing his eyes. "That house... something horrible lives there. I don't know what it is, nor do I particularly want to. But it tried to kill me. And if I go back there, it will finish the job."

Something about the tired resignation in those words gave me the chills. I hated feeling afraid on the job, but I couldn't help it. Although I'd encountered many weirdos throughout my career, this old man wasn't like the rest. I didn't know what to make of him.

"What's going to kill you, Edwin?"

I heard the door slam shut as Keira walked out. I didn't blame her for not wanting to listen. If it were my dad, I'd feel the same.

Edwin let out another long sigh. "Well, there is more than one monster in that place. But the one that drove me to such extremes... he is the one that has tormented me the most. He is the one who killed my wife."

"Didn't your wife die of a stroke?"

"That's what the doctors said. But that's not what really happened. He killed her."

I rested a comforting hand on his shoulder. "Who are you talking about, Edwin?"

"The man with the orange eyes."

Now this was getting interested. "The man with the orange eyes," I repeated, slowly.

Edwin nodded. He had gone pale, his body shaking against the restraints.

"I've been seeing him every day, since we moved in. He's evil. A monster. He killed my wife, and he's going to kill me too."

"Who is this man? A ghost?"

"I don't know what he is. But he certainly isn't human."

I still can't say I believed this was anything paranormal. But every word Edwin spoke sent further shivers down my spine. "Is he a demon?"

"Perhaps. That place is known as 'The House of Demons' after all."

"Did you know about the history of the house before you moved in?"

Edwin shook his head rapidly. "No. Well, perhaps a little, but I didn't believe a word of it. I was a skeptic, just as you appear to be."

I stared down at my notebook; I hadn't written a thing, I was so captured by Edwin's story. "How could you tell?"

He smiled, ever so slightly. "I just could."

I shook my head, swallowing my discomfort. "Well, anyway. You didn't know about the stories?"

"Not much, and I didn't believe them anyway. I moved my family in without a second thought, and for a while, things were okay. But I began seeing things."

He paused for a breath, then continued. "Terrible things. I had the most awful of dreams and visions. People being killed in the most brutal of fashions. Demon creatures lurking in the corners. The floor breaking apart and revealing a portal to Hell. The man with the orange eyes.

"He isn't so much a man as he is a shadow. Just a black silhouette, shaped like a man, with these glowing orange orbs in his face. They are like twin flames, and they never seem to dim. I have seen him every day for the past thirty-something years. He torments me.

"I never told the wife or kids. I didn't want to frighten them. Instead, I hung crosses on the walls and hoped the grace of God would protect us. And to an extent, it did. But the man with orange eyes never left. I would wake up in the middle of the night and find him standing over the bed, watching my wife and I sleep. I'd pull into the driveway in the evening and see him at a window. He never spoke to me directly, but sometimes, I could hear a deep, raspy voice in my head. It would say terrible things."

"Like what?" I asked.

Edwin began shaking even harder. "He would tell me to kill myself, to kill my family. He told me about all the horrible things he had done to those who had lived in the house before. He wanted to drive me mad. I spent every day fighting him.

"Once he realized I wouldn't be so easy to break, he turned on my wife. It only took her two years to fall. He drained the life out of her.

"After Prudence's death, I began hearing scratching sounds in the walls. I thought they might be rats, but that was before the whispers started. And the screams. And the blood."

"Excuse me, blood?"

"Yes. The walls themselves would bleed."

Okay, that was freaky. I glanced behind me at the closed door, wondering if Keira was listening, before turning my attention back to Edwin.

"What else can you tell me?"

"The man with the orange eyes was angry," said Edwin. "He had wanted me to die first, not Prudence. He swore he would make my demise as painful as possible." Edwin's eyes slipped away from me and went to his bandaged arms. "He wanted my blood. He wanted me to suffer. On the day I was admitted to this place, he did something... I don't know what, but it felt as if I had insects crawling beneath my skin. That's why I tore up my arms. The man with the orange eyes was laughing at me. It was terrible. And now, he wants to finish the job. I just know it. I'll never be free. Never..."

Edwin went still of a sudden, closing his eyes. For a moment, I feared he was dead, but the rhythmic rise and fall of his chest proved otherwise. I left the room, passing a white-faced and trembling Keira in the hall.

"I'll call you later," I mumbled, and fled the hospital.

Halfway to my hotel, I took a turn and began driving down the road leading to the House of Demons. Why? Well, the most stubborn part of me still didn't believe Edwin's story, dismissing it as the ramblings of a senile old man, and I wanted to see the house for myself.

The House of Demons turned out to be a towering brick structure with a lopsided roof and butter-yellow door. I pulled up out front and sat there for a moment, going over what Edwin had told me again and again. Then, without thinking, I exited the car and went to stand in the overgrown front lawn.

I titled my head back and stared up at a darkened window, remembering Edwin's account of seeing the man with orange eyes watching him from the other side of the class. I didn't expect to see anything, but my eyes were drawn to that window.

It took the shrill ringing of my phone to finally snap me out of it.

"Hello?"

"Mrs. Johnston!" It was Keira, and she sounded freaked. "Mrs. Johnston, what happened? Are you okay?"

"I'm fine, Keira. Your dad's story just spooked me a bit."

"Where are you now?"

"Well... I'm kind of at the house."

"You're what?" she shrieked, so shrilly I had to pull the phone away from my ear to avoid being deafened. "Mrs. Johnston, do you have any idea how dangerous that place is? Especially with no one home."

"Keira, I-"

"I'm on my way. Stay put."

Five minutes later, Keira's car appeared. She parked it behind mine and rushed over to me, panting, her eyes wild and wet.

"Jesus," I gasped. "Are you okay?"

"Daddy was so upset after you left... he was screaming and rambling... the nurse had to sedate him."

I winced. "I'm so sorry."

"No, it wasn't your fault... it was mine. I should never have called you. Shit, I'm a mess. It's just..."

She broke down in heaving sobs, and I awkwardly put my arms around her. Comforting others has never been my strong suit, particularly if it's a stranger. Keira buried her face in my chest, her body trembling against mine.

"Maybe we should get out of here," I said, peering at the house over the top of Keira's head. I was not expecting to see two floating orange orbs in the window.

"Keira," I hissed. "Don't look, okay?"

"What?"

"Don't. Look. Follow me."

I led her back to my rental car and drove off. When I looked back, the eyes were gone, but the sky above the house seemed darker somehow, as if reflecting a coming storm.

I dropped Keira off at her own house and went to my hotel. I wrote out a rough draft for an article on the House of Demons, but could barely concentrate. The project wasn't going anywhere, and I returned home in defeat.

A month later, Keira e-mailed me to tell me that her father had died. "He killed himself. Somehow, he broke the restraints. He clawed his own eyes out and slit his own throat with a shard of glass from the broken window. I think he wanted to die on his own terms, before the man with orange eyes could get him."

I e-mailed her back, expressing my condolences, but never got a response.

I couldn't stop thinking about that house, and decided to return to that town, to see that place one last time.

The House of Demons stood abandoned when I arrived. Before leaving, I had tracked down the realtor trying to sell the house (no luck, which didn't surprise me) and called her, asking if she would let me in. I explained I was a journalist trying to write a piece on the house. "Will you let me in? I just want to have a quick look around."

The woman sounded hesitant, but agreed. I met her at the house, greeting her politely. She was an older woman with platinum-blonde hair, dressed in a navy blue suit. "I'm Norma. Norma Shaw. It's nice to meet you." She nervous tired, and I felt bad for her.

"You don't have to come in with me," I said.

"Nonsense! I can't let you go in that place alone." She fished a set of keys out of her purse. "How long will you need?"

"Not too long," I assured her. "Just a quick look around."

"Okay, then." Mrs. Shaw gave a painful grin. "Let's go."

The interior of the house was dark and musty, not any different from your average old, abandoned dwelling. I felt no oppressive atmosphere, no creeping sensation of being watched. Nothing to justify why this place was called the House of Demons. But remembering Edwin's story and how he had so brutally killed himself, I tried to keep an open mind.

Mrs. Shaw led me from room to room, and I only lingered long enough to jot down some notes and take a quick look around. I saw nothing noteworthy. But on the way back down the upstairs hall, I paused to look at painting hanging on the wall, Mrs. Shaw several steps ahead. When I turned, she was out of sight.

"Mrs. Shaw?" I called, my voice echoing loudly in the empty space. "Hello?"

No answer.

I hurried in the direction she'd been going, turning a corner and finding her purse lying on the floor, the contents spilled out and scattered around like debris from a train wreck. Surrounding the mess was a pool of dark, coppery-smelling liquid.

Blood.

"Holy fucking shit," I whispered. My head was spinning; I didn't want to believe this was happening.

A wet thunk from behind me made me jump about ten feet into the air and spin around. Mrs. Shaw's head had fallen behind me. Her eyes were wide, her face still ossified in an expression of pure horror. The stump of her neck was ragged and bloody, with about two inches of spine visible. The pearl-white bone had been snapped off, leaving a jagged edge.

I ran, dropping my notebook and pen along the way. I didn't really care where I ended up, as long as I was far away from that terrible scene. I was going so fast that when a gnarled hand twisted itself into my hair, my scalp was nearly torn off.

I screamed and thrashed as something dragged me down the stairs. The creature was snarling and hissing in a deep, guttural voice as it threw open the basement door Mrs. Shaw had shown me earlier and threw me down.

I flew through the cold, musty air and hit the concrete floor so hard it's a wonder every bone in my body didn't shatter. Groaning in pain, I rolled over just in time to see the door slam shut and hear something scuttled away.

Adrenaline drowned out the pain of my injuries, and I managed to stand up. As I fumbled around for a light switch, and my hand touched something soft and fleshy.

"Oh, Jesus, no," I muttered.

A frayed string brushed my face, and I pulled on it; a dim yellow lightbulb flickered to life.

I screamed.

Keira. Or at least, what had once been her. She was dead, her skin purple, black, and blue with decay. The top of her head had been caved in, creating a gory cavern of blood, skin, bone, and brain matter. She had been pinned to the wall by what looked like a rusty, bloodstained railroad spike, hammered right through her chest.

"Oh, my God," I muttered, backing up in shock. "Oh, my God. Oh, my God."

Keira's body twitched. Her head jerked up, and she looked right at me. Her eyes were empty sockets, her once-pretty face a bloated mess of rotting flesh and wriggling white maggots. She opened her mouth, her jaw cracking grotesquely as she did so, and let out a screech.

"No!" I wailed, tripping in my high-heeled pumps and landing flat on my ass. Keira let out another scream, and to this day, I can't truly describe the sound. The best thing I can compare it to is the wail of a banshee, mixed with the braying of a goat and radio static.

Through the overwhelming horror taking over my mind, I suddenly remembered: I still had my purse. And in it was my phone.

The terrible screams filled my ears as I crawled across the dirty concrete floor and snatched up the phone. The screen was cracked, but the device still worked. With shaking fingers, I dialled 911.

"Please!" I gasped as soon as the operator picked up. "Send help!"

"What's your emergency?"

"I'm hurt, and there's... there's something here. Please, just hurry!"

I gave the woman my address, and she assured me that help was on the way. As I lay on my back, in pain, waiting for someone to come and rescue me, Keira's screams began morphing into words.

You shouldn't have come!

She didn't have to tell me twice.

Gradually, I became aware of how hot the basement was getting. I could faintly smell smoke, and the realization that the house was on fire hit me with the force of a nuclear blast. I looked up at Keira's impaled body, saw crackling orange flames. Keira's body was melting, the skin sloughing off her bones. Black smoke poured from her mouth and ears. Then, suddenly, she exploded into a swarm of fat black flies.

The combination of heat, pain, and the maniacal buzzing of a thousand or so flies was maddening. I curled into the fetal position, hands over my ears, and screamed.

The next thing I remember is one of the basement windows breaking and a fireman carrying me out.

"Mother of God, miss, what did they do to you?" he gasped.

I was placed in the back of an ambulance, and before the doors were shut, I caught a glimpse of the house going up in flames, as if the very gates of Hell had opened up inside.

I was airlifted back to Vancouver, where I spent five weeks in the hospital. I had broken bones, bruises, scrapes, gashes, burns, and even some internal bleeding. The House of Demons burned down to nothing but ash. The cause of the fire could not be determined.

After returning home in a wheelchair, still all bandaged up, I began to remember things about my encounter. The twisted, goblin-like appearance of the creature that dragged me to the basement. The glowing orange eyes that glared maliciously at me from the dark just before the fire began. The agonized screams and wails of tortured souls, combining with Keira's own cries, creating a cacophony of terror that nearly crippled me.

Needless to say, I didn't end up writing about The House of Demons.

I can't explain what happened, and that's the hardest part. Not knowing. Now I can honestly say I believe in the paranormal. And it terrifies me. I've seen for myself the horrors that lurk in the shadows, and I can never forget.

Especially after the phone call I received last week.

The call came from an unknown number. I picked it up, expecting to hear "Sorry, wrong number." Instead, there was a strange shuffling noise, and a weak, reedy voice whispering, "Please. Help."

"Excuse me, who is this?"

"Please. Help." Then the line went dead.

The voice sounded familiar, but I couldn't place it. Until that night, as I got ready for bed.

It had been Keira. She barely sounded like herself, but it had definitely been her.

I don't know where Keira is now, and I think it best for my sanity that I never found out.

But wherever it is, I sense that it's even worse than The House of Demons.

I just wish there was something I could do.

The Liver Eater by lhcrow89

There’s an old legend in my hometown of Cherokee, North Carolina. A legend of a shapeshifter/witch who lived in our mountains long ago that fed on the livers of our tribe’s children. My hometown is an Indian reservation and several of our elders still tell the legends our ancestors told. There are many different legends but the one of Spearfinger is probably the most widely known around here (it’s also the most fun to tell the tourists that make their way into town every spring and summer). I remember as a kid, we were warned to not wander too far into the woods when we played, our parents and grandparents joked that Spearfinger would get us.

According to the legend, Spearfinger was killed long ago by a group of our tribe’s warriors who had grown angry at her feeding on our children. It is said she could take the form of anyone she wanted, man or woman, but the only thing she couldn’t change was her dagger-like index finger on her right hand. She would take her chosen form to gain the trust of her selected victim, then she would offer to comb the child’s hair and would run her fingers through the child’s hair until the child fell asleep. Once the child was out, she would then take her finger (which she was said to have kept hidden under a blanket or shawl) and slice open the child and cut out their liver, which she would then devour. The child would feel nothing and she would run her fingers over the wound and it would heal, not leaving even a scratch. She would then wake the child and send him or her on home none the wiser.

As most people know, one can’t live without a liver. Soon after being sent home, the child would become ill and pass away. Eventually everyone began to suspect foul play and many tribal members recalled seeing an elderly-looking woman wandering through the woods as they were out fishing, hunting, etc. Each member said that the woman was very frightening and every time she took a step, the very ground would shake with each step. She was said to have skin that appeared to be hardened like stone.

So, from what I can remember, the group of warriors, led by the tribal medicine man, dug a huge pit out in the woods, then lit a fire so Spearfinger would see the smoke and come looking for children. They hid and listened as her thunderous footsteps came closer, until an unearthly scream pierced their eardrums followed by a loud boom that shook the mountains. They had caught her.

The warriors surrounded the pit and began shooting their arrows and throwing their spears at her, only to see the weapons bounce of her skin and fall to ground broken. A bird called a titmouse (funny name, I know) then landed nearby and began to chirp in a way that sounded almost human, that sounded like Unahv which means “heart”. The warriors all aimed for her chest, but once again, their weapons were wasted. The chickadee then appeared and landed on her right hand, which they then aimed for. It is said that her heart was in the palm of her right hand rather than her chest, which was then pierced by the arrows, finally killing her. At least that’s how I remember it.

The reason I tell you this is because over the last year or so, several of our tribe’s children have gone missing. No witnesses, no leads for a single case. As far as I know, most of the children were last seen playing outside their homes or at school. Several locals have gathered together quite a few times and formed search parties, but none have been able to locate any of the children. The local PD has sent search parties as well, along with the SAR dogs but even the dogs were unable to pick up any scents.

Now I know you’re thinking it’s most likely the work of a kidnapper, or God forbid, maybe a serial killer. Or maybe even a bear (we do live in the mountains after all). That’s what I thought too until about a week ago.

A local couple had been out walking along the sides of a mountain near the edge of town looking for wild onions that our tribe enjoys eating (called ramps). Around here this time of year everyone goes out looking for them to gather, eat, and sell to others. I think non-Natives call them wild leeks? Anyways, they came upon a small clearing and were digging when they discovered the bodies of about nine children, ranging from kindergarten age to high school age, all of whom were identified as some of the missing kids.

Not only is this completely devastating to our community, it also frightening a lot of people because what kind of monster would do this to children? I can’t even begin to imagine the pain the parents are going through; I have a five-year-old son and I can’t imagine life without him. But that’s not even the worst part; the children each had routine autopsies performed to determine the cause of death. Each child was missing their liver. Now I know it’s 2018 and that humans have come up with ways to remove organs from others, but that’s not what scares me. Each of the children found had not a single wound on them. No cuts, no lacerations, no bruises. Not even a scratch…

The Penny Cup Killer by nickrk20

It was unlike any Tuesday morning I'd ever had. A serial killer in a small city in Canada? It seemed nearly unheard of. The "Penny Cup Killer" was quickly making his/her name a sensation in national news. You've all been to a gas station and seen the containers that say "Have a penny? Leave a penny. Need a penny? Take a penny." This person was working in a similar fashion, except their slogan seemed to be "Have a victim? Leave a victim. Need a victim? Take a victim."

The Penny Cup Killer's latest victim was always found somewhere in the house of his newest victim. I am a freelance reporter, I just go where the story goes. When a twenty-something year old woman was kidnapped in a small city, I thought I'd just go and check out what type of carnage it created. A week passed by with no leads. Cristina Richards vanished without a trace on her way home from her shift at the local nursing home, gone into thin air. After a few more days, some more disturbing news arose. Cristina Richards had been found. Found in the home of Emily Mortenson, found with her throat slashed, and a blindfold over her eyes. She was hanging in Emily's pantry. As for Emily? She was the next target of the Penny Cup Killer. Police tried to make a connection between Cristina and Emily, but to no avail. Cristina was a brunette, Emily was a redhead. Cristina was a nurse, Emily was a hair stylist. The killer left zero trace of anything, Cristina's body was completely free of prints. The coroner stated the blindfold over her eyes was a basic bandana that could be purchased at any dollar store, and the laceration to her throat was by some sort of hunting knife.

Five days passed since Emily's disappearance, when the third victim was taken. Like Cristina, Emily was found in the home of a bartender named Sandra LaBlanc. Also, like Cristina, Emily's throat was slashed, and she was blindfolded. The difference, with Sandra, was that she had a roommate, Carly. Sandra's roommate was out of town visiting her parents, and when she came back, she opened her closet to discover Emily's body. When the police arrived, they asked Carly if she had been attacked. Carly said no, and that she couldn't get a hold of her roommate. Sandra LaBlanc had become the latest victim of the Penny Cup Killer, and he/she waited until Sandra was alone. Again, there were no leads. The kidnappings were all at random times, the killings were days apart. The entire city was on high alert, young women were encouraged to not go anywhere alone, it was extremely rare for a place like this to have something like this happen. People demanded answers from the local police chief, but he had nothing to give.

A week later, I was just about to go to sleep in my hotel room, I heard the police scanner go off. Sandra LeBlanc was found, just like the others. The difference this time? She was found in her own home, in the same place the killer placed Emily Mortenson. Carly was nowhere to be found. It isn't unusual for serial killers to return to the scene of the crime to relieve their deeds, but it seemed so bold for the killer to return for Carly. Carly was taken seemingly in the middle of the day, and Sandra's estimated time of death was just four days before hand. Police assumed he just wanted to complete the set, but I wasn't so sure. Cristina Richards, Emily Mortenson, Sandra LaBlanc, and now Carly Betts. Four victims approximately three weeks apart. If the timeline with Carly is similar to Sandra, she's still alive.

Police have seemingly exhausted all options, but I may have found a connection. All four women were members of a local woman's only Yoga studio. I visited the studio, "Open Palms Open Minds" it was called. They were hesitant to give me much information, being a freelance reporter, I don't have any credentials, so they might've assumed I was just some creep. The employees all seemed relatively normal, but they would absolutely not let me sit in on the classes. They have a very strict "no males" policy. No male teachers, no male students. That leads me to believe that the Penny Cup Killer is almost certainly, a woman. It's the only lead that's been discovered.

I returned to my hotel room and turned on CBC. Carly Betts was found murdered, same MO as the other victims. She was found in the home of a woman named Valerie Randle, who like the others was now a victim herself. Carly was murdered less than 48 hours after her disappearance, which completely disregards the Penny Cup Killer's previous pattern. The timeline was sped up, but why? My hunch is that I spoke with the Penny Cup Killer today at the yoga studio, caused them to panic, and they disposed of their victim as quickly as possible. As expected, Valerie was indeed a part of the same yoga studio. I'll be returning there tomorrow with more questions.

There is something wrong with my house...there has always been by artsystrangegirl

Hello there, I’m new to Reddit as I just discovered that this is the best place to find help and solve some seriously scary and creepy problems in my life.

First of all, a little background. I’m from a little town in Northern Italy, so excuse my terrible, terrible English! Anyway, in this town there aren’t more than 1000 people and most of them are basically in their sixties or seventies. They are VERY, VERY superstitious and this is why I needed to find another place to explain my situation, and this place is Reddit.

My family is composed of 4 people: my dad, my mum, my little sister and I. My mother’s parents are still alive whilst my father’s parents died two/three years ago (keep this in mind).

I have a pretty normal life... so I think, at least. I go to high school and I’m specialising in languages (English, Spanish and Russian), I spend my free time studying and trying to put everything I can into my brain, because there is nothing I love more than studying and reading. Next year, I will go to the university but since it’s fairly near my house I think I’ll live with my parents at least for the first year.

This is where the main problem lays: they want me to live in my father’s dead parents house. And I swear you guys: I don’t want to. Trust me, I don’t believe in God or anything like that but I do feel like there is something in that house. I don’t think it is a bad entity, I think it could be my grandpa, he left us very surprisingly and unexpectedly and I know that entities that die in this way tend to remain in our reality because they still have something to do or whatever.

So here’s the thing: my parents and my sister don’t believe me... and they are the religious people in the family!!!

But you guys I kid you not A WHOLE LOT has happened in that house and I want to share it with you so that we can find out what is happening.

Moreover, a bunch of strange things have been happening to my family (including my mother’s mother, who was friends with my deceased grandpa, the father of my father) even outside that house.

So let’s jump into what has happened lately in my life that pushed me to publish this. My mother has been complaining lately because she keeps seeing double numbers like 22:22, 18:18... stuff like that ALL THE MOTHEREFFIN TIME. At first, I just laughed at her because I just thought it was normal: everybody can see double numbers, nothing strange, right? But that wasn’t until these double numbers kept showing consistently in our ordinary life: a bill, the clock, a grade at school, the temperature, tv channels and so on, but my mother and I are the only ones in the family experiencing this at the time. And then, the creepiest thing happened to me. So I was sleeping and lucid dreaming as always. In my dream, I was in an old office with a very important man here in Italy, he was the president of a football club and he was also very important in economics and politics before he died years ago. He was telling me something, but all of a sudden he started saying repeatedly “17 and 17: keep an eye on that OK, myname?” C O N T I N O U S L Y I woke up being very disturbed by that dream and thought about that the whole day at school, until I realised that the 7/1 is the day before my dead grandpa’s bday and the 17 (of December) is the day before my grandpa died. This has totally creeped me out.

But things got “worse”. As I kept seeing more and more double numbers and my mother always less and less, I started hearing noises coming from my grandpa’s house. At first, I thought it was their cat but then it turned out that my father wanted him to stay outside the house during the day (don’t ask me why, my father is strange lol).

So I was very creeped out and when my mother proposed that I invited my friends from high school to sleep over in THAT house, that was a H U G E no-no. However, she was able to convince me. So I prepared everything to sleep in the living room all together (we were 3) and the night arrived fast. Before we fell asleep, one of my friends checked the clock and she said: “Oh hey, it’s 24:24” I was S O S C A R E D, but I actually didn’t want to scare her so I just laughed and tried to sleep.

The day after, however, I told her everything about my strange problems with double numbers and she wanted to check what 24 meant in a book of numbers which I bought in order to understand these double numbers I keep seeing.

So we checked and at first I was disappointed: it didn’t have a meaning for me! But all of a sudden my friend started to cry, shivering. “This is crazy!” She told me “You were right!”

“What, why?” I asked.

“The number 24 says: you are facing new challenges, but don’t worry, you have two helpers there with you.” She cried “you and myotherfriend promised to help me with my grades at school, remember?”

And all of a sudden, it was all clear to me: my grandpa knew that this friend of mine wasn’t exactly Einstein and he died before meeting my fourth friend (who didn’t sleep there that night), so he knew only me and my other friend who could help the other one with her grades. And that’s why the numbers didn’t have a meaning to me: I didn’t see the numbers, my friend did... it was a message for her!

What do you think you guys? I have A LOT of other episodes that will help to complete this puzzle and I would love to share it with you so that we can solve this strange case together.

What do you think this is? Why do I see all those numbers with a significant meaning and why do I keep hearing strange noises?

....

UPDATE!!!! I was going to publish this but I wanted to check the grammar before and I was doing it with my headphones on... but with no music because I’m a weird girl. So my mum and my dad were in the kitchen and I heard them talking. “I saw him again” my mother said. “Who?” My father asked. “Your father. His shadow, again!” “What the heck. You need to sleep more!” “But I swear I saw him! You MUST NOT tell it to the girls. myname could like to investigate deeper”

WHAT THE HECK DOES THIS MEAN?? Guys, I need your help!

We Found A Cellphone On A Recent Camping Trip In Michigan With A Disturbing Video On It by nevergoingcampingaga

I don't know if this is the place for this, but this is a very strange and unnerving situation. Due to the short improvement in the weather recently, me and a friend went camping. We chose a place near our town. We will not give away the name due to anonymity, but it is a forested area near a small river with various campgrounds and bike trails. The paths go back deep into the wilderness, which is where me and my friend (lets call him T) decided to go camping. We drove a good 15 miles into the national forest and set up camp out there. We didn't usually camp out this far, but we were feeling brave. Hell it was only a 2 night trip and we had all our supplies and enough food, and a nice 1970s camper just in case it got too cold. It is the kind of camper that is built onto the box of a truck. We were confident this trip would go well.

We decided to simply set up camp the first day. We couldn't get a proper fire pit dug since the ground was just un-thawing, so we used a small portable grill we brought with us. We set up some lanterns, a few chairs, and sat outside drinking beer and kicking back. Things got strange around dusk though...

Around the time the sun went down we began noticing occasional red lights, and strange indescribable sounds. you know, almost like a voice carrying in the wind that resonates, unnaturally? It really is hard to explain. We have never been out that deep before, but then again we also may just hadn't noticed until this point.

We were both unnerved but ignored it up until around 10pm. Things went from kinda-sorta weird, to strange and creepy fast. The red lights seemed to pop up and float in the forest around us, only to vanish with seconds. It got more and more intense, when in the distance, i saw a pair of bright orange eyes, 8-12 feet off of the ground, staring at us. We were terrified. We were too drunk to drive out so we went into the camper, locked it, and went to sleep. Thankfully we were drunk.

The next day everything was normal. We discovered something we hadn't the day before. There was a trail leading off into the woods where we saw the eyes last night. Despite all common sense we were intrigued and decided to follow it. T had a rifle just in case we ran into anything dangerous. The morning was very foggy and bleak and the trees still had no leaves, giving the forest a very dead, unnerving feel. The further we went on this path the foggier it got, until we could only see about 50 feet at most. After roughly 1 mile down this path we came across a small dilapidated cabin. It was more like a small shed with windows. It was filled with old boxes and had a huge hole in the floor, leading to a creepy basement. There was also a small fire-pit nearby with some buckets and bricks around it. This was a small clearing surrounded by dense brush and trees. This place made us feel uneasy.

I noticed something in the grass nearby and picked it up. It was an old cellphone. It looked destroyed. We checked the sd card and it was fine. We decided to keep it and check it out later. At this point i noticed the path led further into the woods to my left. We decided against it after finding this cabin. We were getting seriously creeped out and we were hearing the strange sounds again. We heard movement in the dense foggy forest on to our left and something strange happened. We both sort of blacked out and full on sprinted back down the way we came. By the time we realized what we were doing the sun was setting and it was getting dark. FUCK we had no idea what happened but I used my flashlight to illuminate the trail and we jogged back. It was the strangest thing... almost like a short fugue state for 7 or so hours. How did we get here? When we got back to camp we decided to stay in the trailer for the night. We had enough time outside that day.

That night we were having trouble sleeping and decided to smoke some green. As we were smoking i noticed the red lights out the windows again. I figured i was being paranoid and ignored it. After we were done we went to bed. T was asleep quickly but i just couldn't sleep. I had a strange feeling. Like we were being watched... I listened intently but heard nothing. The feeling was growing and i was beginning to feel legitimately scared, almost to the point where i didn't want to look at the window. I hid under my covers and the sense of dread only rose higher. I decided to slowly peer out at the window. It was at this point i realized that this sense of being watched had evolved to a sense of absolute terror. I slowly looked out from under my blanket and throughout the camper, and the windows. The camper was dark, and my friend was snoring. I looked over at the back window. Nothing. At this point I looked over to the side window. MY blood ran cold and I froze and nearly screamed. The glowing orange eyes we had seen the night before where peering in and motionless. I looked directly at these eyes in frozen terror for several minutes, the creature began bashing the door with near impossible force, and I finally came to, grabbing my pistol and firing without thinking. A horrible scream rang out and something, whatever it was, fled. My friend woke up screaming and i told him everything was alright, but we were leaving.

I let him sleep in the camper and got into the drivers seat and started the truck up. To my absolute horror, hundreds of pairs of red and orange eyes appeared when the headlights went on. They scattered. I peeled the fuck out of there and drove out as fast as i could. When we got back we checked the SD card we had found in the phone near the cabin.

It contained some music, some personal photos, and a single video. This video was of the cabin we had seen, at night, with the owner of the phone and another person venturing further on the trail than we did. The creepy sounds we had heard were clear throughout the video, and towards the end a pair of eyes appeared on the trail, glitching the video, before the people filming ran as fast as they could back, now surrounded by the red lights, only for the phone to be dropped as the Filmer yells. At this point the video ended. We were horrified. This video was so similar to the things we had seen that night.. too similar. Something happened there... something terrible... we aren't going camping again. All this was was solid proof to stay the fuck out of that forest. I have no idea what became of the owner of the phone. There was no other trace of them...

The video from the sd card located here https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RamILOotljw